{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947022920728","data":{"timestamp":" 947022920728"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 46ce070a-00e0-4494-ac64-d1e6e4a19938"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_2-1-3"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947022921453","data":{"timestamp":" 947022921453"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 46ce070a-00e0-4494-ac64-d1e6e4a19938"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_1_2-1-3"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947022996379","data":{"timestamp":" 947022996379"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" db56dffe-dcdf-4e0a-abff-2292e4eb8a8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" muhimu_vyakula-muhimu-vigumu-uongo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" muhimu"," userResponse":" muhimu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023029367","data":{"timestamp":" 947023029367"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" db56dffe-dcdf-4e0a-abff-2292e4eb8a8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mdogo_tayari-mdogo-mkewe-shamba"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mdogo"," userResponse":" mdogo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023109332","data":{"timestamp":" 947023109332"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" db56dffe-dcdf-4e0a-abff-2292e4eb8a8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyingine_furaha-nyingine-mwalimu-kubwa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" nyingine"," userResponse":" nyingine"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023157508","data":{"timestamp":" 947023157507"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" db56dffe-dcdf-4e0a-abff-2292e4eb8a8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbaya_nyingine-ardhi-mbaya-mpira"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mbaya"," userResponse":" mbaya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023249328","data":{"timestamp":" 947023249328"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" db56dffe-dcdf-4e0a-abff-2292e4eb8a8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vile_chungu-kidogo-jina-vile"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" vile"," userResponse":" vile"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023273258","data":{"timestamp":" 947023273258"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" db56dffe-dcdf-4e0a-abff-2292e4eb8a8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tajiri_nami-meno-wapi-tajiri"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" tajiri"," userResponse":" tajiri"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023349562","data":{"timestamp":" 947023349562"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" db56dffe-dcdf-4e0a-abff-2292e4eb8a8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tena_la-mti-tena-fisi"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" tena"," userResponse":" tena"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023379850","data":{"timestamp":" 947023379850"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" db56dffe-dcdf-4e0a-abff-2292e4eb8a8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" barabara_barabara-hizi-pa-rudi"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" barabara"," userResponse":" barabara"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023408160","data":{"timestamp":" 947023408159"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" db56dffe-dcdf-4e0a-abff-2292e4eb8a8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" barabara_barabara-hizi-pa-rudi"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023408295","data":{"timestamp":" 947023408295"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" db56dffe-dcdf-4e0a-abff-2292e4eb8a8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ____________"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023415169","data":{"timestamp":" 947023415169"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" db56dffe-dcdf-4e0a-abff-2292e4eb8a8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023428919","data":{"timestamp":" 947023428919"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 4327ffd8-abfa-4261-a8f9-0dff458e3367"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_3-2-1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023434549","data":{"timestamp":" 947023434549"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 4327ffd8-abfa-4261-a8f9-0dff458e3367"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_1-3-2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023439485","data":{"timestamp":" 947023439485"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 4327ffd8-abfa-4261-a8f9-0dff458e3367"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_4-3-2"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023442042","data":{"timestamp":" 947023442041"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 4327ffd8-abfa-4261-a8f9-0dff458e3367"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_3_4-3-2"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:R..R.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023450847","data":{"timestamp":" 947023450847"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 4327ffd8-abfa-4261-a8f9-0dff458e3367"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_3_4-3-2"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023459193","data":{"timestamp":" 947023459192"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 4327ffd8-abfa-4261-a8f9-0dff458e3367"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_3_4-3-2"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023465247","data":{"timestamp":" 947023465246"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 4327ffd8-abfa-4261-a8f9-0dff458e3367"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_3_4-3-2"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023471266","data":{"timestamp":" 947023471266"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 4327ffd8-abfa-4261-a8f9-0dff458e3367"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_3_4-3-2"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023477734","data":{"timestamp":" 947023477734"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 4327ffd8-abfa-4261-a8f9-0dff458e3367"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_3_4-3-2"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023487271","data":{"timestamp":" 947023487271"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika bustani ndogo jijini kulikuwa na mti mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023487977","data":{"timestamp":" 947023487976"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika bustani ndogo jijini kulikuwa na mti mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023488492","data":{"timestamp":" 947023488491"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika bustani ndogo jijini kulikuwa na mti mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" NDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023489333","data":{"timestamp":" 947023489333"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika bustani ndogo jijini kulikuwa na mti mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIJINI"," userResponse":" JIJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023490242","data":{"timestamp":" 947023490241"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika bustani ndogo jijini kulikuwa na mti mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" KULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023490456","data":{"timestamp":" 947023490456"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika bustani ndogo jijini kulikuwa na mti mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023490839","data":{"timestamp":" 947023490838"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika bustani ndogo jijini kulikuwa na mti mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023491652","data":{"timestamp":" 947023491652"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika bustani ndogo jijini kulikuwa na mti mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBWA"," userResponse":" MKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023494151","data":{"timestamp":" 947023494150"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023494895","data":{"timestamp":" 947023494894"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGI"," userResponse":" WENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023495700","data":{"timestamp":" 947023495699"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIISHI"," userResponse":" WALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023496413","data":{"timestamp":" 947023496412"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023496902","data":{"timestamp":" 947023496901"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023497119","data":{"timestamp":" 947023497119"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023497569","data":{"timestamp":" 947023497569"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023497947","data":{"timestamp":" 947023497946"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUU"," userResponse":" HUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023500575","data":{"timestamp":" 947023500575"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikki alikuwa mmoja wa kindi aliyependa kuongea mambo makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIISHI"," userResponse":" PALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023500989","data":{"timestamp":" 947023500989"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikki alikuwa mmoja wa kindi aliyependa kuongea mambo makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" PIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023501722","data":{"timestamp":" 947023501722"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikki alikuwa mmoja wa kindi aliyependa kuongea mambo makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JAMII"," userResponse":" JAMII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023501827","data":{"timestamp":" 947023501827"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikki alikuwa mmoja wa kindi aliyependa kuongea mambo makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023502449","data":{"timestamp":" 947023502449"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikki alikuwa mmoja wa kindi aliyependa kuongea mambo makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINDI"," userResponse":" KINDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023504818","data":{"timestamp":" 947023504818"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikki alikuwa mmoja wa kindi aliyependa kuongea mambo makubwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIKKI"," userResponse":" VIKKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023505673","data":{"timestamp":" 947023505673"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikki alikuwa mmoja wa kindi aliyependa kuongea mambo makubwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023506268","data":{"timestamp":" 947023506268"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikki alikuwa mmoja wa kindi aliyependa kuongea mambo makubwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023506458","data":{"timestamp":" 947023506458"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikki alikuwa mmoja wa kindi aliyependa kuongea mambo makubwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023507137","data":{"timestamp":" 947023507136"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikki alikuwa mmoja wa kindi aliyependa kuongea mambo makubwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINDI"," userResponse":" KINDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023508112","data":{"timestamp":" 947023508111"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikki alikuwa mmoja wa kindi aliyependa kuongea mambo makubwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEPENDA"," userResponse":" ALIYEPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023508852","data":{"timestamp":" 947023508852"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikki alikuwa mmoja wa kindi aliyependa kuongea mambo makubwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONGEA"," userResponse":" KUONGEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023509366","data":{"timestamp":" 947023509366"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikki alikuwa mmoja wa kindi aliyependa kuongea mambo makubwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBO"," userResponse":" MAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023510365","data":{"timestamp":" 947023510364"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikki alikuwa mmoja wa kindi aliyependa kuongea mambo makubwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKUBWA"," userResponse":" MAKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023512665","data":{"timestamp":" 947023512664"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Binamuye Kato kutoka Msitu wa Mbali alikuwa amekuja kumtembelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BINAMUYE"," userResponse":" BINAMUYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023513075","data":{"timestamp":" 947023513075"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Binamuye Kato kutoka Msitu wa Mbali alikuwa amekuja kumtembelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATO"," userResponse":" KATO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023514417","data":{"timestamp":" 947023514416"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Binamuye Kato kutoka Msitu wa Mbali alikuwa amekuja kumtembelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023515312","data":{"timestamp":" 947023515311"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Binamuye Kato kutoka Msitu wa Mbali alikuwa amekuja kumtembelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITU"," userResponse":" MSITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023515550","data":{"timestamp":" 947023515550"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Binamuye Kato kutoka Msitu wa Mbali alikuwa amekuja kumtembelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023516204","data":{"timestamp":" 947023516203"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Binamuye Kato kutoka Msitu wa Mbali alikuwa amekuja kumtembelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" MBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023517305","data":{"timestamp":" 947023517305"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Binamuye Kato kutoka Msitu wa Mbali alikuwa amekuja kumtembelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023518065","data":{"timestamp":" 947023518065"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Binamuye Kato kutoka Msitu wa Mbali alikuwa amekuja kumtembelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEKUJA"," userResponse":" AMEKUJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023519239","data":{"timestamp":" 947023519239"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Binamuye Kato kutoka Msitu wa Mbali alikuwa amekuja kumtembelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMTEMBELEA"," userResponse":" KUMTEMBELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023522118","data":{"timestamp":" 947023522118"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wanyama wote walioishi katika ile bustani ndogo walienda kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIONI"," userResponse":" JIONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023522662","data":{"timestamp":" 947023522661"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wanyama wote walioishi katika ile bustani ndogo walienda kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023523605","data":{"timestamp":" 947023523604"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wanyama wote walioishi katika ile bustani ndogo walienda kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023524198","data":{"timestamp":" 947023524198"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wanyama wote walioishi katika ile bustani ndogo walienda kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023525208","data":{"timestamp":" 947023525206"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wanyama wote walioishi katika ile bustani ndogo walienda kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIOISHI"," userResponse":" WALIOISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023525812","data":{"timestamp":" 947023525811"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wanyama wote walioishi katika ile bustani ndogo walienda kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023526221","data":{"timestamp":" 947023526221"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wanyama wote walioishi katika ile bustani ndogo walienda kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023526909","data":{"timestamp":" 947023526909"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wanyama wote walioishi katika ile bustani ndogo walienda kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023527380","data":{"timestamp":" 947023527380"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wanyama wote walioishi katika ile bustani ndogo walienda kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" NDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023528562","data":{"timestamp":" 947023528562"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wanyama wote walioishi katika ile bustani ndogo walienda kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIENDA"," userResponse":" WALIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023529369","data":{"timestamp":" 947023529369"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wanyama wote walioishi katika ile bustani ndogo walienda kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULALA"," userResponse":" KULALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023531790","data":{"timestamp":" 947023531790"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara walisikia sauti kubwa ikitoka uwanja uliokuwa karibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023532590","data":{"timestamp":" 947023532589"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara walisikia sauti kubwa ikitoka uwanja uliokuwa karibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALISIKIA"," userResponse":" WALISIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023533244","data":{"timestamp":" 947023533243"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara walisikia sauti kubwa ikitoka uwanja uliokuwa karibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023534060","data":{"timestamp":" 947023534060"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara walisikia sauti kubwa ikitoka uwanja uliokuwa karibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023535272","data":{"timestamp":" 947023535272"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara walisikia sauti kubwa ikitoka uwanja uliokuwa karibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKITOKA"," userResponse":" IKITOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023535894","data":{"timestamp":" 947023535894"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara walisikia sauti kubwa ikitoka uwanja uliokuwa karibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UWANJA"," userResponse":" UWANJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023536750","data":{"timestamp":" 947023536749"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara walisikia sauti kubwa ikitoka uwanja uliokuwa karibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOKUWA"," userResponse":" ULIOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023537425","data":{"timestamp":" 947023537425"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara walisikia sauti kubwa ikitoka uwanja uliokuwa karibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023540390","data":{"timestamp":" 947023540390"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato na kindi wengine waliona mashine kubwa ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATO"," userResponse":" KATO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023540581","data":{"timestamp":" 947023540580"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato na kindi wengine waliona mashine kubwa ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023541340","data":{"timestamp":" 947023541340"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato na kindi wengine waliona mashine kubwa ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINDI"," userResponse":" KINDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023542294","data":{"timestamp":" 947023542294"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato na kindi wengine waliona mashine kubwa ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023543308","data":{"timestamp":" 947023543307"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato na kindi wengine waliona mashine kubwa ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIONA"," userResponse":" WALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023544050","data":{"timestamp":" 947023544049"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato na kindi wengine waliona mashine kubwa ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHINE"," userResponse":" MASHINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023544641","data":{"timestamp":" 947023544640"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato na kindi wengine waliona mashine kubwa ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023544823","data":{"timestamp":" 947023544823"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato na kindi wengine waliona mashine kubwa ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023545708","data":{"timestamp":" 947023545707"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato na kindi wengine waliona mashine kubwa ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANJANO"," userResponse":" MANJANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023548345","data":{"timestamp":" 947023548345"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliona pia wanaume waliovalia kofia ngumu za manjano wakionyesha kwa vidole ile bustani ndogo na nyumba zingine zilizokuwa upande mwingine wa barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIONA"," userResponse":" WALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023548940","data":{"timestamp":" 947023548939"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliona pia wanaume waliovalia kofia ngumu za manjano wakionyesha kwa vidole ile bustani ndogo na nyumba zingine zilizokuwa upande mwingine wa barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" PIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023549883","data":{"timestamp":" 947023549883"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Waliona pia wanaume waliovalia kofia ngumu za manjano wakionyesha kwa vidole ile bustani ndogo na nyumba zingine zilizokuwa upande mwingine wa barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023549963","data":{"timestamp":" 947023549963"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliona pia wanaume waliovalia kofia ngumu za manjano wakionyesha kwa vidole ile bustani ndogo na nyumba zingine zilizokuwa upande mwingine wa barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" PIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023556811","data":{"timestamp":" 947023556810"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0a355e8f-7116-4441-828d-70b236bf8713"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Waliona pia wanaume waliovalia kofia ngumu za manjano wakionyesha kwa vidole ile bustani ndogo na nyumba zingine zilizokuwa upande mwingine wa barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023573414","data":{"timestamp":" 947023573413"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 243a613d-74ae-4df8-9442-786d14f72b5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023575558","data":{"timestamp":" 947023575558"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 243a613d-74ae-4df8-9442-786d14f72b5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023578644","data":{"timestamp":" 947023578644"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 243a613d-74ae-4df8-9442-786d14f72b5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023592081","data":{"timestamp":" 947023592081"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 243a613d-74ae-4df8-9442-786d14f72b5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023600744","data":{"timestamp":" 947023600744"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 243a613d-74ae-4df8-9442-786d14f72b5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023609689","data":{"timestamp":" 947023609689"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 243a613d-74ae-4df8-9442-786d14f72b5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023618359","data":{"timestamp":" 947023618359"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 243a613d-74ae-4df8-9442-786d14f72b5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023628125","data":{"timestamp":" 947023628124"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 243a613d-74ae-4df8-9442-786d14f72b5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023628132","data":{"timestamp":" 947023628132"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 243a613d-74ae-4df8-9442-786d14f72b5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023636274","data":{"timestamp":" 947023636274"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 243a613d-74ae-4df8-9442-786d14f72b5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023649717","data":{"timestamp":" 947023649717"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" e185a118-959a-45be-a035-c11b2568ccdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kigoe changu cha kuchezea tenisi kimepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIGOE"," userResponse":" KIGOE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023650340","data":{"timestamp":" 947023650340"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" e185a118-959a-45be-a035-c11b2568ccdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kigoe changu cha kuchezea tenisi kimepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHANGU"," userResponse":" CHANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023650529","data":{"timestamp":" 947023650529"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" e185a118-959a-45be-a035-c11b2568ccdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kigoe changu cha kuchezea tenisi kimepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023651432","data":{"timestamp":" 947023651432"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" e185a118-959a-45be-a035-c11b2568ccdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kigoe changu cha kuchezea tenisi kimepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZEA"," userResponse":" KUCHEZEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023652070","data":{"timestamp":" 947023652070"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" e185a118-959a-45be-a035-c11b2568ccdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kigoe changu cha kuchezea tenisi kimepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENISI"," userResponse":" TENISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023653062","data":{"timestamp":" 947023653061"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" e185a118-959a-45be-a035-c11b2568ccdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kigoe changu cha kuchezea tenisi kimepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMEPOTEA"," userResponse":" KIMEPOTEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023655431","data":{"timestamp":" 947023655431"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" e185a118-959a-45be-a035-c11b2568ccdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui kimeenda wapi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIJUI"," userResponse":" SIJUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023656174","data":{"timestamp":" 947023656174"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" e185a118-959a-45be-a035-c11b2568ccdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui kimeenda wapi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMEENDA"," userResponse":" KIMEENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023656787","data":{"timestamp":" 947023656787"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" e185a118-959a-45be-a035-c11b2568ccdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui kimeenda wapi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" WAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023660777","data":{"timestamp":" 947023660776"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" e185a118-959a-45be-a035-c11b2568ccdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKITAFUTA"," userResponse":" NILIKITAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023661184","data":{"timestamp":" 947023661184"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" e185a118-959a-45be-a035-c11b2568ccdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMA"," userResponse":" NYUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023661419","data":{"timestamp":" 947023661419"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" e185a118-959a-45be-a035-c11b2568ccdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023662090","data":{"timestamp":" 947023662090"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" e185a118-959a-45be-a035-c11b2568ccdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLANGO"," userResponse":" MLANGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023664661","data":{"timestamp":" 947023664660"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" e185a118-959a-45be-a035-c11b2568ccdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023665767","data":{"timestamp":" 947023665766"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" e185a118-959a-45be-a035-c11b2568ccdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKUKIONA"," userResponse":" SIKUKIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023669374","data":{"timestamp":" 947023669374"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" e185a118-959a-45be-a035-c11b2568ccdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta juu ya kabati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKITAFUTA"," userResponse":" NILIKITAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023669642","data":{"timestamp":" 947023669642"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" e185a118-959a-45be-a035-c11b2568ccdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta juu ya kabati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023669843","data":{"timestamp":" 947023669843"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" e185a118-959a-45be-a035-c11b2568ccdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta juu ya kabati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023670595","data":{"timestamp":" 947023670594"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" e185a118-959a-45be-a035-c11b2568ccdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta juu ya kabati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KABATI"," userResponse":" KABATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023673166","data":{"timestamp":" 947023673165"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" e185a118-959a-45be-a035-c11b2568ccdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023674271","data":{"timestamp":" 947023674270"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" e185a118-959a-45be-a035-c11b2568ccdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKUKIONA"," userResponse":" SIKUKIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023678127","data":{"timestamp":" 947023678127"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" e185a118-959a-45be-a035-c11b2568ccdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta chini ya kitanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKITAFUTA"," userResponse":" NILIKITAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023678507","data":{"timestamp":" 947023678507"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" e185a118-959a-45be-a035-c11b2568ccdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta chini ya kitanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023678601","data":{"timestamp":" 947023678601"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" e185a118-959a-45be-a035-c11b2568ccdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta chini ya kitanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023679314","data":{"timestamp":" 947023679313"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" e185a118-959a-45be-a035-c11b2568ccdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta chini ya kitanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITANDA"," userResponse":" KITANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023681703","data":{"timestamp":" 947023681703"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" e185a118-959a-45be-a035-c11b2568ccdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hapo sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023682106","data":{"timestamp":" 947023682105"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" e185a118-959a-45be-a035-c11b2568ccdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hapo sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023683109","data":{"timestamp":" 947023683108"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" e185a118-959a-45be-a035-c11b2568ccdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hapo sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKUKIONA"," userResponse":" SIKUKIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023686544","data":{"timestamp":" 947023686544"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" e185a118-959a-45be-a035-c11b2568ccdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta ndani ya sanduku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKITAFUTA"," userResponse":" NILIKITAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023686937","data":{"timestamp":" 947023686937"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" e185a118-959a-45be-a035-c11b2568ccdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta ndani ya sanduku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023687000","data":{"timestamp":" 947023687000"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" e185a118-959a-45be-a035-c11b2568ccdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta ndani ya sanduku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023687745","data":{"timestamp":" 947023687743"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" e185a118-959a-45be-a035-c11b2568ccdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta ndani ya sanduku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANDUKU"," userResponse":" SANDUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023690258","data":{"timestamp":" 947023690258"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" e185a118-959a-45be-a035-c11b2568ccdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapakuwa na dalili yake pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023691043","data":{"timestamp":" 947023691043"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" e185a118-959a-45be-a035-c11b2568ccdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapakuwa na dalili yake pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPAKUWA"," userResponse":" HAPAKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023691256","data":{"timestamp":" 947023691256"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" e185a118-959a-45be-a035-c11b2568ccdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapakuwa na dalili yake pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023691940","data":{"timestamp":" 947023691940"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" e185a118-959a-45be-a035-c11b2568ccdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapakuwa na dalili yake pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DALILI"," userResponse":" DALILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023692254","data":{"timestamp":" 947023692254"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" e185a118-959a-45be-a035-c11b2568ccdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapakuwa na dalili yake pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023692767","data":{"timestamp":" 947023692767"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" e185a118-959a-45be-a035-c11b2568ccdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapakuwa na dalili yake pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023696390","data":{"timestamp":" 947023696390"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" e185a118-959a-45be-a035-c11b2568ccdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta katika dari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKITAFUTA"," userResponse":" NILIKITAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023696983","data":{"timestamp":" 947023696983"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" e185a118-959a-45be-a035-c11b2568ccdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta katika dari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023697390","data":{"timestamp":" 947023697389"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" e185a118-959a-45be-a035-c11b2568ccdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta katika dari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DARI"," userResponse":" DARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023700855","data":{"timestamp":" 947023700855"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" e185a118-959a-45be-a035-c11b2568ccdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia hapa na pale nikaangalia kila mahali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIANGALIA"," userResponse":" NILIANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023701608","data":{"timestamp":" 947023701608"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" e185a118-959a-45be-a035-c11b2568ccdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia hapa na pale nikaangalia kila mahali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" HAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023702076","data":{"timestamp":" 947023702075"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" e185a118-959a-45be-a035-c11b2568ccdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia hapa na pale nikaangalia kila mahali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023702648","data":{"timestamp":" 947023702648"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" e185a118-959a-45be-a035-c11b2568ccdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia hapa na pale nikaangalia kila mahali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023703842","data":{"timestamp":" 947023703842"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" e185a118-959a-45be-a035-c11b2568ccdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia hapa na pale nikaangalia kila mahali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKAANGALIA"," userResponse":" NIKAANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023704466","data":{"timestamp":" 947023704465"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" e185a118-959a-45be-a035-c11b2568ccdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia hapa na pale nikaangalia kila mahali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023705049","data":{"timestamp":" 947023705049"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" e185a118-959a-45be-a035-c11b2568ccdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia hapa na pale nikaangalia kila mahali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" MAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023707567","data":{"timestamp":" 947023707567"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" e185a118-959a-45be-a035-c11b2568ccdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023708665","data":{"timestamp":" 947023708664"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" e185a118-959a-45be-a035-c11b2568ccdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKUKIONA"," userResponse":" SIKUKIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023720390","data":{"timestamp":" 947023720389"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" e185a118-959a-45be-a035-c11b2568ccdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023720468","data":{"timestamp":" 947023720468"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" e185a118-959a-45be-a035-c11b2568ccdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKUKIONA"," userResponse":" SIKUKIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023727298","data":{"timestamp":" 947023727297"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" e185a118-959a-45be-a035-c11b2568ccdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023734020","data":{"timestamp":" 947023734019"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" e185a118-959a-45be-a035-c11b2568ccdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023740354","data":{"timestamp":" 947023740354"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" e185a118-959a-45be-a035-c11b2568ccdf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023752333","data":{"timestamp":" 947023752332"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikuwa anamalizia kuweka nguo zake katika begi ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023753169","data":{"timestamp":" 947023753168"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikuwa anamalizia kuweka nguo zake katika begi ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023754210","data":{"timestamp":" 947023754209"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikuwa anamalizia kuweka nguo zake katika begi ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAMALIZIA"," userResponse":" ANAMALIZIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023754870","data":{"timestamp":" 947023754870"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikuwa anamalizia kuweka nguo zake katika begi ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWEKA"," userResponse":" KUWEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023755289","data":{"timestamp":" 947023755289"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikuwa anamalizia kuweka nguo zake katika begi ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUO"," userResponse":" NGUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023755718","data":{"timestamp":" 947023755718"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikuwa anamalizia kuweka nguo zake katika begi ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023756234","data":{"timestamp":" 947023756234"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikuwa anamalizia kuweka nguo zake katika begi ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023756673","data":{"timestamp":" 947023756673"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikuwa anamalizia kuweka nguo zake katika begi ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BEGI"," userResponse":" BEGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023757148","data":{"timestamp":" 947023757148"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikuwa anamalizia kuweka nguo zake katika begi ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" NDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023760525","data":{"timestamp":" 947023760525"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akipita mlangoni alinikumbatia na kusema Kwa heri kwa sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023761443","data":{"timestamp":" 947023761442"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akipita mlangoni alinikumbatia na kusema Kwa heri kwa sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIPITA"," userResponse":" AKIPITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023762384","data":{"timestamp":" 947023762384"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akipita mlangoni alinikumbatia na kusema Kwa heri kwa sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLANGONI"," userResponse":" MLANGONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023763937","data":{"timestamp":" 947023763936"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akipita mlangoni alinikumbatia na kusema Kwa heri kwa sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINIKUMBATIA"," userResponse":" ALINIKUMBATIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023764169","data":{"timestamp":" 947023764168"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akipita mlangoni alinikumbatia na kusema Kwa heri kwa sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023764888","data":{"timestamp":" 947023764888"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akipita mlangoni alinikumbatia na kusema Kwa heri kwa sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSEMA"," userResponse":" KUSEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023765411","data":{"timestamp":" 947023765411"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akipita mlangoni alinikumbatia na kusema Kwa heri kwa sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023765853","data":{"timestamp":" 947023765853"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akipita mlangoni alinikumbatia na kusema Kwa heri kwa sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERI"," userResponse":" HERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023766051","data":{"timestamp":" 947023766051"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akipita mlangoni alinikumbatia na kusema Kwa heri kwa sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023766701","data":{"timestamp":" 947023766700"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akipita mlangoni alinikumbatia na kusema Kwa heri kwa sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023769972","data":{"timestamp":" 947023769972"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unaenda wapi mama?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAENDA"," userResponse":" UNAENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023770458","data":{"timestamp":" 947023770458"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unaenda wapi mama?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" WAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023771174","data":{"timestamp":" 947023771172"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unaenda wapi mama?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023774073","data":{"timestamp":" 947023774073"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nilimwuliza huku nikimwangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIMWULIZA"," userResponse":" NILIMWULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023774463","data":{"timestamp":" 947023774463"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nilimwuliza huku nikimwangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023775719","data":{"timestamp":" 947023775719"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nilimwuliza huku nikimwangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKIMWANGALIA"," userResponse":" NIKIMWANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023778830","data":{"timestamp":" 947023778829"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia nikitaka kumfuata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIANZA"," userResponse":" NILIANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023779663","data":{"timestamp":" 947023779662"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia nikitaka kumfuata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIA"," userResponse":" KULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023780630","data":{"timestamp":" 947023780629"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia nikitaka kumfuata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKITAKA"," userResponse":" NIKITAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023781766","data":{"timestamp":" 947023781765"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia nikitaka kumfuata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMFUATA"," userResponse":" KUMFUATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023784549","data":{"timestamp":" 947023784549"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini baba alinibeba juu begani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023784972","data":{"timestamp":" 947023784972"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini baba alinibeba juu begani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023785951","data":{"timestamp":" 947023785951"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini baba alinibeba juu begani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINIBEBA"," userResponse":" ALINIBEBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023786725","data":{"timestamp":" 947023786725"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini baba alinibeba juu begani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023787279","data":{"timestamp":" 947023787279"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini baba alinibeba juu begani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BEGANI"," userResponse":" BEGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023787813","data":{"timestamp":" 947023787813"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini baba alinibeba juu begani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAKE"," userResponse":" KWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023790775","data":{"timestamp":" 947023790775"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba alisema Mamako anaenda hospitalini kujifungua mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023791594","data":{"timestamp":" 947023791594"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba alisema Mamako anaenda hospitalini kujifungua mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023792604","data":{"timestamp":" 947023792604"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba alisema Mamako anaenda hospitalini kujifungua mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKO"," userResponse":" MAMAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023793203","data":{"timestamp":" 947023793203"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba alisema Mamako anaenda hospitalini kujifungua mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAENDA"," userResponse":" ANAENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023794467","data":{"timestamp":" 947023794467"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba alisema Mamako anaenda hospitalini kujifungua mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HOSPITALINI"," userResponse":" HOSPITALINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023795597","data":{"timestamp":" 947023795597"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba alisema Mamako anaenda hospitalini kujifungua mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJIFUNGUA"," userResponse":" KUJIFUNGUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023796361","data":{"timestamp":" 947023796361"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba alisema Mamako anaenda hospitalini kujifungua mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023800114","data":{"timestamp":" 947023800113"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliposikia mtoto niliacha kulia na kumwangalia baba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIPOSIKIA"," userResponse":" NILIPOSIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023801148","data":{"timestamp":" 947023801148"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliposikia mtoto niliacha kulia na kumwangalia baba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023802030","data":{"timestamp":" 947023802030"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliposikia mtoto niliacha kulia na kumwangalia baba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIACHA"," userResponse":" NILIACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023802604","data":{"timestamp":" 947023802604"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliposikia mtoto niliacha kulia na kumwangalia baba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIA"," userResponse":" KULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023803017","data":{"timestamp":" 947023803017"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliposikia mtoto niliacha kulia na kumwangalia baba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023803869","data":{"timestamp":" 947023803868"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliposikia mtoto niliacha kulia na kumwangalia baba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWANGALIA"," userResponse":" KUMWANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023804329","data":{"timestamp":" 947023804329"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliposikia mtoto niliacha kulia na kumwangalia baba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023806518","data":{"timestamp":" 947023806518"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  nilimuuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023807079","data":{"timestamp":" 947023807079"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  nilimuuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023807754","data":{"timestamp":" 947023807754"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  nilimuuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAENDA"," userResponse":" ANAENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023808487","data":{"timestamp":" 947023808487"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  nilimuuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMPATA"," userResponse":" KUMPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023809001","data":{"timestamp":" 947023809001"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  nilimuuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023810231","data":{"timestamp":" 947023810230"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  nilimuuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HOSPITALINI"," userResponse":" HOSPITALINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023813220","data":{"timestamp":" 947023813219"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  nilimuuliza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIMUULIZA"," userResponse":" NILIMUULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023816131","data":{"timestamp":" 947023816131"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba alinikalisha juu ya kiti kidogo na kusema Nitakueleza kwa nini anaenda kumpata mtoto hospitalini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023817352","data":{"timestamp":" 947023817351"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba alinikalisha juu ya kiti kidogo na kusema Nitakueleza kwa nini anaenda kumpata mtoto hospitalini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINIKALISHA"," userResponse":" ALINIKALISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023817684","data":{"timestamp":" 947023817684"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba alinikalisha juu ya kiti kidogo na kusema Nitakueleza kwa nini anaenda kumpata mtoto hospitalini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023817893","data":{"timestamp":" 947023817892"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba alinikalisha juu ya kiti kidogo na kusema Nitakueleza kwa nini anaenda kumpata mtoto hospitalini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023818314","data":{"timestamp":" 947023818314"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba alinikalisha juu ya kiti kidogo na kusema Nitakueleza kwa nini anaenda kumpata mtoto hospitalini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITI"," userResponse":" KITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023818889","data":{"timestamp":" 947023818889"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba alinikalisha juu ya kiti kidogo na kusema Nitakueleza kwa nini anaenda kumpata mtoto hospitalini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" KIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023819068","data":{"timestamp":" 947023819068"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba alinikalisha juu ya kiti kidogo na kusema Nitakueleza kwa nini anaenda kumpata mtoto hospitalini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023819749","data":{"timestamp":" 947023819748"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba alinikalisha juu ya kiti kidogo na kusema Nitakueleza kwa nini anaenda kumpata mtoto hospitalini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSEMA"," userResponse":" KUSEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023821289","data":{"timestamp":" 947023821289"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba alinikalisha juu ya kiti kidogo na kusema Nitakueleza kwa nini anaenda kumpata mtoto hospitalini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAKUELEZA"," userResponse":" NITAKUELEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023821507","data":{"timestamp":" 947023821507"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba alinikalisha juu ya kiti kidogo na kusema Nitakueleza kwa nini anaenda kumpata mtoto hospitalini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023821944","data":{"timestamp":" 947023821943"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba alinikalisha juu ya kiti kidogo na kusema Nitakueleza kwa nini anaenda kumpata mtoto hospitalini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023822587","data":{"timestamp":" 947023822587"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba alinikalisha juu ya kiti kidogo na kusema Nitakueleza kwa nini anaenda kumpata mtoto hospitalini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAENDA"," userResponse":" ANAENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023823366","data":{"timestamp":" 947023823366"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba alinikalisha juu ya kiti kidogo na kusema Nitakueleza kwa nini anaenda kumpata mtoto hospitalini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMPATA"," userResponse":" KUMPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023823917","data":{"timestamp":" 947023823917"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba alinikalisha juu ya kiti kidogo na kusema Nitakueleza kwa nini anaenda kumpata mtoto hospitalini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023825153","data":{"timestamp":" 947023825152"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba alinikalisha juu ya kiti kidogo na kusema Nitakueleza kwa nini anaenda kumpata mtoto hospitalini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HOSPITALINI"," userResponse":" HOSPITALINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023828725","data":{"timestamp":" 947023828725"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisikiliza kwa makini aliponielezea ingawa sikuelewa kwa nini hakumpata mtoto akiwa nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILISIKILIZA"," userResponse":" NILISIKILIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023829026","data":{"timestamp":" 947023829026"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisikiliza kwa makini aliponielezea ingawa sikuelewa kwa nini hakumpata mtoto akiwa nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023830199","data":{"timestamp":" 947023830198"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisikiliza kwa makini aliponielezea ingawa sikuelewa kwa nini hakumpata mtoto akiwa nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKINI"," userResponse":" MAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023832062","data":{"timestamp":" 947023832062"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisikiliza kwa makini aliponielezea ingawa sikuelewa kwa nini hakumpata mtoto akiwa nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPONIELEZEA"," userResponse":" ALIPONIELEZEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023832886","data":{"timestamp":" 947023832885"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisikiliza kwa makini aliponielezea ingawa sikuelewa kwa nini hakumpata mtoto akiwa nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INGAWA"," userResponse":" INGAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023833842","data":{"timestamp":" 947023833842"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisikiliza kwa makini aliponielezea ingawa sikuelewa kwa nini hakumpata mtoto akiwa nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKUELEWA"," userResponse":" SIKUELEWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023834096","data":{"timestamp":" 947023834096"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisikiliza kwa makini aliponielezea ingawa sikuelewa kwa nini hakumpata mtoto akiwa nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023834645","data":{"timestamp":" 947023834644"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisikiliza kwa makini aliponielezea ingawa sikuelewa kwa nini hakumpata mtoto akiwa nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023835720","data":{"timestamp":" 947023835719"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisikiliza kwa makini aliponielezea ingawa sikuelewa kwa nini hakumpata mtoto akiwa nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUMPATA"," userResponse":" HAKUMPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023836243","data":{"timestamp":" 947023836243"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisikiliza kwa makini aliponielezea ingawa sikuelewa kwa nini hakumpata mtoto akiwa nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023836687","data":{"timestamp":" 947023836686"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisikiliza kwa makini aliponielezea ingawa sikuelewa kwa nini hakumpata mtoto akiwa nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIWA"," userResponse":" AKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023837547","data":{"timestamp":" 947023837547"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisikiliza kwa makini aliponielezea ingawa sikuelewa kwa nini hakumpata mtoto akiwa nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023840551","data":{"timestamp":" 947023840550"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomaliza kunielezea nilimuuliza Je ataendelea kunipenda hata baada ya kurudi na mtoto mwingine?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOMALIZA"," userResponse":" ALIPOMALIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023841684","data":{"timestamp":" 947023841683"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomaliza kunielezea nilimuuliza Je ataendelea kunipenda hata baada ya kurudi na mtoto mwingine?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNIELEZEA"," userResponse":" KUNIELEZEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023843165","data":{"timestamp":" 947023843164"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomaliza kunielezea nilimuuliza Je ataendelea kunipenda hata baada ya kurudi na mtoto mwingine?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIMUULIZA"," userResponse":" NILIMUULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023843965","data":{"timestamp":" 947023843964"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomaliza kunielezea nilimuuliza Je ataendelea kunipenda hata baada ya kurudi na mtoto mwingine?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023845744","data":{"timestamp":" 947023845744"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomaliza kunielezea nilimuuliza Je ataendelea kunipenda hata baada ya kurudi na mtoto mwingine?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ATAENDELEA"," userResponse":" ATAENDELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023846741","data":{"timestamp":" 947023846741"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomaliza kunielezea nilimuuliza Je ataendelea kunipenda hata baada ya kurudi na mtoto mwingine?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNIPENDA"," userResponse":" KUNIPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023847173","data":{"timestamp":" 947023847172"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomaliza kunielezea nilimuuliza Je ataendelea kunipenda hata baada ya kurudi na mtoto mwingine?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023847715","data":{"timestamp":" 947023847715"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomaliza kunielezea nilimuuliza Je ataendelea kunipenda hata baada ya kurudi na mtoto mwingine?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023847895","data":{"timestamp":" 947023847895"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomaliza kunielezea nilimuuliza Je ataendelea kunipenda hata baada ya kurudi na mtoto mwingine?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947023847954","data":{"timestamp":" 947023847954"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 67106ab0-f35d-4466-87ad-8630eaa4b485"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomaliza kunielezea nilimuuliza Je ataendelea kunipenda hata baada ya kurudi na mtoto mwingine?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024425823","data":{"timestamp":" 947024425823"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikuwa anamalizia kuweka nguo zake katika begi ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024426647","data":{"timestamp":" 947024426646"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikuwa anamalizia kuweka nguo zake katika begi ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024427681","data":{"timestamp":" 947024427681"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikuwa anamalizia kuweka nguo zake katika begi ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAMALIZIA"," userResponse":" ANAMALIZIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024428351","data":{"timestamp":" 947024428350"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikuwa anamalizia kuweka nguo zake katika begi ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWEKA"," userResponse":" KUWEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024428764","data":{"timestamp":" 947024428764"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikuwa anamalizia kuweka nguo zake katika begi ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUO"," userResponse":" NGUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024429188","data":{"timestamp":" 947024429188"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikuwa anamalizia kuweka nguo zake katika begi ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024429690","data":{"timestamp":" 947024429690"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikuwa anamalizia kuweka nguo zake katika begi ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024430123","data":{"timestamp":" 947024430123"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikuwa anamalizia kuweka nguo zake katika begi ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BEGI"," userResponse":" BEGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024430591","data":{"timestamp":" 947024430591"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikuwa anamalizia kuweka nguo zake katika begi ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" NDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024433981","data":{"timestamp":" 947024433981"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akipita mlangoni alinikumbatia na kusema Kwa heri kwa sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024434884","data":{"timestamp":" 947024434884"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akipita mlangoni alinikumbatia na kusema Kwa heri kwa sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIPITA"," userResponse":" AKIPITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024435841","data":{"timestamp":" 947024435841"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akipita mlangoni alinikumbatia na kusema Kwa heri kwa sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLANGONI"," userResponse":" MLANGONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024437388","data":{"timestamp":" 947024437387"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akipita mlangoni alinikumbatia na kusema Kwa heri kwa sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINIKUMBATIA"," userResponse":" ALINIKUMBATIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024437617","data":{"timestamp":" 947024437617"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akipita mlangoni alinikumbatia na kusema Kwa heri kwa sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024438332","data":{"timestamp":" 947024438332"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akipita mlangoni alinikumbatia na kusema Kwa heri kwa sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSEMA"," userResponse":" KUSEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024438850","data":{"timestamp":" 947024438850"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akipita mlangoni alinikumbatia na kusema Kwa heri kwa sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024439287","data":{"timestamp":" 947024439287"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akipita mlangoni alinikumbatia na kusema Kwa heri kwa sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERI"," userResponse":" HERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024439487","data":{"timestamp":" 947024439486"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akipita mlangoni alinikumbatia na kusema Kwa heri kwa sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024440134","data":{"timestamp":" 947024440134"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akipita mlangoni alinikumbatia na kusema Kwa heri kwa sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024443268","data":{"timestamp":" 947024443268"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unaenda wapi mama?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAENDA"," userResponse":" UNAENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024443749","data":{"timestamp":" 947024443749"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unaenda wapi mama?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" WAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024444465","data":{"timestamp":" 947024444464"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unaenda wapi mama?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024447259","data":{"timestamp":" 947024447259"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nilimwuliza huku nikimwangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIMWULIZA"," userResponse":" NILIMWULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024447648","data":{"timestamp":" 947024447648"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nilimwuliza huku nikimwangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024448892","data":{"timestamp":" 947024448892"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nilimwuliza huku nikimwangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKIMWANGALIA"," userResponse":" NIKIMWANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024452013","data":{"timestamp":" 947024452012"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia nikitaka kumfuata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIANZA"," userResponse":" NILIANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024452845","data":{"timestamp":" 947024452844"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia nikitaka kumfuata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIA"," userResponse":" KULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024453802","data":{"timestamp":" 947024453801"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia nikitaka kumfuata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKITAKA"," userResponse":" NIKITAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024454949","data":{"timestamp":" 947024454946"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia nikitaka kumfuata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMFUATA"," userResponse":" KUMFUATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024457677","data":{"timestamp":" 947024457677"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini baba alinibeba juu begani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024458111","data":{"timestamp":" 947024458111"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini baba alinibeba juu begani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024459084","data":{"timestamp":" 947024459084"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini baba alinibeba juu begani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINIBEBA"," userResponse":" ALINIBEBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024459871","data":{"timestamp":" 947024459870"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini baba alinibeba juu begani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024460434","data":{"timestamp":" 947024460434"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini baba alinibeba juu begani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BEGANI"," userResponse":" BEGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024460974","data":{"timestamp":" 947024460974"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini baba alinibeba juu begani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAKE"," userResponse":" KWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024463825","data":{"timestamp":" 947024463825"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba alisema Mamako anaenda hospitalini kujifungua mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024464653","data":{"timestamp":" 947024464653"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba alisema Mamako anaenda hospitalini kujifungua mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024465668","data":{"timestamp":" 947024465668"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba alisema Mamako anaenda hospitalini kujifungua mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKO"," userResponse":" MAMAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024466271","data":{"timestamp":" 947024466271"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba alisema Mamako anaenda hospitalini kujifungua mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAENDA"," userResponse":" ANAENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024467531","data":{"timestamp":" 947024467531"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba alisema Mamako anaenda hospitalini kujifungua mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HOSPITALINI"," userResponse":" HOSPITALINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024468670","data":{"timestamp":" 947024468670"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba alisema Mamako anaenda hospitalini kujifungua mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJIFUNGUA"," userResponse":" KUJIFUNGUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024469434","data":{"timestamp":" 947024469434"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba alisema Mamako anaenda hospitalini kujifungua mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024473018","data":{"timestamp":" 947024473018"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliposikia mtoto niliacha kulia na kumwangalia baba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIPOSIKIA"," userResponse":" NILIPOSIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024474052","data":{"timestamp":" 947024474052"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliposikia mtoto niliacha kulia na kumwangalia baba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024474936","data":{"timestamp":" 947024474936"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliposikia mtoto niliacha kulia na kumwangalia baba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIACHA"," userResponse":" NILIACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024475509","data":{"timestamp":" 947024475509"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliposikia mtoto niliacha kulia na kumwangalia baba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIA"," userResponse":" KULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024475922","data":{"timestamp":" 947024475922"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliposikia mtoto niliacha kulia na kumwangalia baba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024476766","data":{"timestamp":" 947024476766"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliposikia mtoto niliacha kulia na kumwangalia baba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWANGALIA"," userResponse":" KUMWANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024477219","data":{"timestamp":" 947024477218"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliposikia mtoto niliacha kulia na kumwangalia baba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024479282","data":{"timestamp":" 947024479282"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  nilimuuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024479838","data":{"timestamp":" 947024479838"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  nilimuuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024480491","data":{"timestamp":" 947024480491"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  nilimuuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAENDA"," userResponse":" ANAENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024481214","data":{"timestamp":" 947024481214"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  nilimuuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMPATA"," userResponse":" KUMPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024481728","data":{"timestamp":" 947024481728"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  nilimuuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024482942","data":{"timestamp":" 947024482942"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  nilimuuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HOSPITALINI"," userResponse":" HOSPITALINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024485895","data":{"timestamp":" 947024485895"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  nilimuuliza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIMUULIZA"," userResponse":" NILIMUULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024488651","data":{"timestamp":" 947024488651"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba alinikalisha juu ya kiti kidogo na kusema Nitakueleza kwa nini anaenda kumpata mtoto hospitalini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024489856","data":{"timestamp":" 947024489856"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba alinikalisha juu ya kiti kidogo na kusema Nitakueleza kwa nini anaenda kumpata mtoto hospitalini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINIKALISHA"," userResponse":" ALINIKALISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024490179","data":{"timestamp":" 947024490179"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba alinikalisha juu ya kiti kidogo na kusema Nitakueleza kwa nini anaenda kumpata mtoto hospitalini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024490382","data":{"timestamp":" 947024490382"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba alinikalisha juu ya kiti kidogo na kusema Nitakueleza kwa nini anaenda kumpata mtoto hospitalini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024490796","data":{"timestamp":" 947024490796"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba alinikalisha juu ya kiti kidogo na kusema Nitakueleza kwa nini anaenda kumpata mtoto hospitalini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITI"," userResponse":" KITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024491349","data":{"timestamp":" 947024491349"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba alinikalisha juu ya kiti kidogo na kusema Nitakueleza kwa nini anaenda kumpata mtoto hospitalini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" KIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024491503","data":{"timestamp":" 947024491503"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba alinikalisha juu ya kiti kidogo na kusema Nitakueleza kwa nini anaenda kumpata mtoto hospitalini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024492177","data":{"timestamp":" 947024492177"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba alinikalisha juu ya kiti kidogo na kusema Nitakueleza kwa nini anaenda kumpata mtoto hospitalini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSEMA"," userResponse":" KUSEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024493711","data":{"timestamp":" 947024493711"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba alinikalisha juu ya kiti kidogo na kusema Nitakueleza kwa nini anaenda kumpata mtoto hospitalini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAKUELEZA"," userResponse":" NITAKUELEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024493925","data":{"timestamp":" 947024493925"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba alinikalisha juu ya kiti kidogo na kusema Nitakueleza kwa nini anaenda kumpata mtoto hospitalini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024494350","data":{"timestamp":" 947024494350"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba alinikalisha juu ya kiti kidogo na kusema Nitakueleza kwa nini anaenda kumpata mtoto hospitalini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024494984","data":{"timestamp":" 947024494984"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba alinikalisha juu ya kiti kidogo na kusema Nitakueleza kwa nini anaenda kumpata mtoto hospitalini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAENDA"," userResponse":" ANAENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024495730","data":{"timestamp":" 947024495730"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba alinikalisha juu ya kiti kidogo na kusema Nitakueleza kwa nini anaenda kumpata mtoto hospitalini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMPATA"," userResponse":" KUMPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024496273","data":{"timestamp":" 947024496273"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba alinikalisha juu ya kiti kidogo na kusema Nitakueleza kwa nini anaenda kumpata mtoto hospitalini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024497488","data":{"timestamp":" 947024497487"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba alinikalisha juu ya kiti kidogo na kusema Nitakueleza kwa nini anaenda kumpata mtoto hospitalini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HOSPITALINI"," userResponse":" HOSPITALINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024501129","data":{"timestamp":" 947024501128"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisikiliza kwa makini aliponielezea ingawa sikuelewa kwa nini hakumpata mtoto akiwa nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILISIKILIZA"," userResponse":" NILISIKILIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024501422","data":{"timestamp":" 947024501422"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisikiliza kwa makini aliponielezea ingawa sikuelewa kwa nini hakumpata mtoto akiwa nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024502589","data":{"timestamp":" 947024502589"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisikiliza kwa makini aliponielezea ingawa sikuelewa kwa nini hakumpata mtoto akiwa nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKINI"," userResponse":" MAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024504459","data":{"timestamp":" 947024504459"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisikiliza kwa makini aliponielezea ingawa sikuelewa kwa nini hakumpata mtoto akiwa nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPONIELEZEA"," userResponse":" ALIPONIELEZEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024505288","data":{"timestamp":" 947024505288"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisikiliza kwa makini aliponielezea ingawa sikuelewa kwa nini hakumpata mtoto akiwa nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INGAWA"," userResponse":" INGAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024506218","data":{"timestamp":" 947024506217"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisikiliza kwa makini aliponielezea ingawa sikuelewa kwa nini hakumpata mtoto akiwa nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKUELEWA"," userResponse":" SIKUELEWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024506462","data":{"timestamp":" 947024506461"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisikiliza kwa makini aliponielezea ingawa sikuelewa kwa nini hakumpata mtoto akiwa nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024507003","data":{"timestamp":" 947024507002"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisikiliza kwa makini aliponielezea ingawa sikuelewa kwa nini hakumpata mtoto akiwa nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024508082","data":{"timestamp":" 947024508081"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisikiliza kwa makini aliponielezea ingawa sikuelewa kwa nini hakumpata mtoto akiwa nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUMPATA"," userResponse":" HAKUMPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024508593","data":{"timestamp":" 947024508592"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisikiliza kwa makini aliponielezea ingawa sikuelewa kwa nini hakumpata mtoto akiwa nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024509043","data":{"timestamp":" 947024509042"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisikiliza kwa makini aliponielezea ingawa sikuelewa kwa nini hakumpata mtoto akiwa nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIWA"," userResponse":" AKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024509887","data":{"timestamp":" 947024509887"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisikiliza kwa makini aliponielezea ingawa sikuelewa kwa nini hakumpata mtoto akiwa nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024512945","data":{"timestamp":" 947024512942"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomaliza kunielezea nilimuuliza Je ataendelea kunipenda hata baada ya kurudi na mtoto mwingine?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOMALIZA"," userResponse":" ALIPOMALIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024514081","data":{"timestamp":" 947024514080"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomaliza kunielezea nilimuuliza Je ataendelea kunipenda hata baada ya kurudi na mtoto mwingine?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNIELEZEA"," userResponse":" KUNIELEZEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024515562","data":{"timestamp":" 947024515561"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomaliza kunielezea nilimuuliza Je ataendelea kunipenda hata baada ya kurudi na mtoto mwingine?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIMUULIZA"," userResponse":" NILIMUULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024516364","data":{"timestamp":" 947024516364"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomaliza kunielezea nilimuuliza Je ataendelea kunipenda hata baada ya kurudi na mtoto mwingine?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024518136","data":{"timestamp":" 947024518135"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomaliza kunielezea nilimuuliza Je ataendelea kunipenda hata baada ya kurudi na mtoto mwingine?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ATAENDELEA"," userResponse":" ATAENDELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024519107","data":{"timestamp":" 947024519106"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomaliza kunielezea nilimuuliza Je ataendelea kunipenda hata baada ya kurudi na mtoto mwingine?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNIPENDA"," userResponse":" KUNIPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024519545","data":{"timestamp":" 947024519545"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomaliza kunielezea nilimuuliza Je ataendelea kunipenda hata baada ya kurudi na mtoto mwingine?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024520085","data":{"timestamp":" 947024520084"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomaliza kunielezea nilimuuliza Je ataendelea kunipenda hata baada ya kurudi na mtoto mwingine?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024520248","data":{"timestamp":" 947024520247"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomaliza kunielezea nilimuuliza Je ataendelea kunipenda hata baada ya kurudi na mtoto mwingine?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024520899","data":{"timestamp":" 947024520899"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomaliza kunielezea nilimuuliza Je ataendelea kunipenda hata baada ya kurudi na mtoto mwingine?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUDI"," userResponse":" KURUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024521118","data":{"timestamp":" 947024521117"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomaliza kunielezea nilimuuliza Je ataendelea kunipenda hata baada ya kurudi na mtoto mwingine?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024521670","data":{"timestamp":" 947024521670"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomaliza kunielezea nilimuuliza Je ataendelea kunipenda hata baada ya kurudi na mtoto mwingine?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024522615","data":{"timestamp":" 947024522615"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomaliza kunielezea nilimuuliza Je ataendelea kunipenda hata baada ya kurudi na mtoto mwingine?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024525546","data":{"timestamp":" 947024525546"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alinibeba na kuniambia Tutakupenda wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABANGU"," userResponse":" BABANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024526576","data":{"timestamp":" 947024526575"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alinibeba na kuniambia Tutakupenda wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINIBEBA"," userResponse":" ALINIBEBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024526774","data":{"timestamp":" 947024526774"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alinibeba na kuniambia Tutakupenda wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024527707","data":{"timestamp":" 947024527706"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alinibeba na kuniambia Tutakupenda wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNIAMBIA"," userResponse":" KUNIAMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024529996","data":{"timestamp":" 947024529996"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alinibeba na kuniambia Tutakupenda wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUTAKUPENDA"," userResponse":" TUTAKUPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024530839","data":{"timestamp":" 947024530838"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alinibeba na kuniambia Tutakupenda wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024531602","data":{"timestamp":" 947024531601"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alinibeba na kuniambia Tutakupenda wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024534960","data":{"timestamp":" 947024534960"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninaweza kumwandikia barua akiwa huko?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAWEZA"," userResponse":" NINAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024536224","data":{"timestamp":" 947024536224"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninaweza kumwandikia barua akiwa huko?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWANDIKIA"," userResponse":" KUMWANDIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024536708","data":{"timestamp":" 947024536708"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninaweza kumwandikia barua akiwa huko?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARUA"," userResponse":" BARUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024537483","data":{"timestamp":" 947024537483"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninaweza kumwandikia barua akiwa huko?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIWA"," userResponse":" AKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024538326","data":{"timestamp":" 947024538326"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninaweza kumwandikia barua akiwa huko?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKO"," userResponse":" HUKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024541502","data":{"timestamp":" 947024541501"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nilimuuliza baba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIMUULIZA"," userResponse":" NILIMUULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024541894","data":{"timestamp":" 947024541894"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nilimuuliza baba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024544795","data":{"timestamp":" 947024544795"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni hiyo nilianza kumtungia mama barua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIONI"," userResponse":" JIONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024545396","data":{"timestamp":" 947024545396"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni hiyo nilianza kumtungia mama barua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024546360","data":{"timestamp":" 947024546360"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni hiyo nilianza kumtungia mama barua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIANZA"," userResponse":" NILIANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024547253","data":{"timestamp":" 947024547253"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni hiyo nilianza kumtungia mama barua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMTUNGIA"," userResponse":" KUMTUNGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024547738","data":{"timestamp":" 947024547738"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni hiyo nilianza kumtungia mama barua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024548217","data":{"timestamp":" 947024548217"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni hiyo nilianza kumtungia mama barua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARUA"," userResponse":" BARUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024551523","data":{"timestamp":" 947024551522"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilirarua karatasi kutoka daftari langu na kuanza kuandika..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIRARUA"," userResponse":" NILIRARUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024552391","data":{"timestamp":" 947024552391"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilirarua karatasi kutoka daftari langu na kuanza kuandika..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARATASI"," userResponse":" KARATASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024552882","data":{"timestamp":" 947024552881"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilirarua karatasi kutoka daftari langu na kuanza kuandika..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024553573","data":{"timestamp":" 947024553572"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilirarua karatasi kutoka daftari langu na kuanza kuandika..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DAFTARI"," userResponse":" DAFTARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024554052","data":{"timestamp":" 947024554052"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilirarua karatasi kutoka daftari langu na kuanza kuandika..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LANGU"," userResponse":" LANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024554571","data":{"timestamp":" 947024554571"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilirarua karatasi kutoka daftari langu na kuanza kuandika..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024555127","data":{"timestamp":" 947024555126"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilirarua karatasi kutoka daftari langu na kuanza kuandika..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUANZA"," userResponse":" KUANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024555969","data":{"timestamp":" 947024555969"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilirarua karatasi kutoka daftari langu na kuanza kuandika..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUANDIKA"," userResponse":" KUANDIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024559044","data":{"timestamp":" 947024559043"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama mama baba alisema kwamba umeenda kumleta mtoto mwingine..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024560165","data":{"timestamp":" 947024560165"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama mama baba alisema kwamba umeenda kumleta mtoto mwingine..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024561135","data":{"timestamp":" 947024561135"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama mama baba alisema kwamba umeenda kumleta mtoto mwingine..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024562122","data":{"timestamp":" 947024562122"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama mama baba alisema kwamba umeenda kumleta mtoto mwingine..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024562853","data":{"timestamp":" 947024562853"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama mama baba alisema kwamba umeenda kumleta mtoto mwingine..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024563792","data":{"timestamp":" 947024563792"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama mama baba alisema kwamba umeenda kumleta mtoto mwingine..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMEENDA"," userResponse":" UMEENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024564503","data":{"timestamp":" 947024564503"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama mama baba alisema kwamba umeenda kumleta mtoto mwingine..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMLETA"," userResponse":" KUMLETA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024565067","data":{"timestamp":" 947024565067"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama mama baba alisema kwamba umeenda kumleta mtoto mwingine..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024565931","data":{"timestamp":" 947024565931"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama mama baba alisema kwamba umeenda kumleta mtoto mwingine..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024591460","data":{"timestamp":" 947024591460"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mama mama baba alisema kwamba umeenda kumleta mtoto mwingine..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024591534","data":{"timestamp":" 947024591534"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama mama baba alisema kwamba umeenda kumleta mtoto mwingine..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024607327","data":{"timestamp":" 947024607327"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mama mama baba alisema kwamba umeenda kumleta mtoto mwingine..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024618784","data":{"timestamp":" 947024618784"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mama mama baba alisema kwamba umeenda kumleta mtoto mwingine..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024624981","data":{"timestamp":" 947024624981"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" bef3fd08-3118-4625-b63f-ac9314612994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mama mama baba alisema kwamba umeenda kumleta mtoto mwingine..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024635154","data":{"timestamp":" 947024635154"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" fe9e3dd9-7e0c-413b-82b6-72f0f3ec26e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliondokea mvulana mmoja aliyeitwa Demane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024635754","data":{"timestamp":" 947024635754"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" fe9e3dd9-7e0c-413b-82b6-72f0f3ec26e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliondokea mvulana mmoja aliyeitwa Demane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024635953","data":{"timestamp":" 947024635952"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" fe9e3dd9-7e0c-413b-82b6-72f0f3ec26e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliondokea mvulana mmoja aliyeitwa Demane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024636346","data":{"timestamp":" 947024636345"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" fe9e3dd9-7e0c-413b-82b6-72f0f3ec26e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliondokea mvulana mmoja aliyeitwa Demane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024637822","data":{"timestamp":" 947024637822"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" fe9e3dd9-7e0c-413b-82b6-72f0f3ec26e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliondokea mvulana mmoja aliyeitwa Demane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIONDOKEA"," userResponse":" PALIONDOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024638483","data":{"timestamp":" 947024638483"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" fe9e3dd9-7e0c-413b-82b6-72f0f3ec26e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliondokea mvulana mmoja aliyeitwa Demane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVULANA"," userResponse":" MVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024639266","data":{"timestamp":" 947024639266"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" fe9e3dd9-7e0c-413b-82b6-72f0f3ec26e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliondokea mvulana mmoja aliyeitwa Demane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024640365","data":{"timestamp":" 947024640365"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" fe9e3dd9-7e0c-413b-82b6-72f0f3ec26e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliondokea mvulana mmoja aliyeitwa Demane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEITWA"," userResponse":" ALIYEITWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024641060","data":{"timestamp":" 947024641060"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" fe9e3dd9-7e0c-413b-82b6-72f0f3ec26e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliondokea mvulana mmoja aliyeitwa Demane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DEMANE"," userResponse":" DEMANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024643486","data":{"timestamp":" 947024643486"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" fe9e3dd9-7e0c-413b-82b6-72f0f3ec26e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024643713","data":{"timestamp":" 947024643713"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" fe9e3dd9-7e0c-413b-82b6-72f0f3ec26e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024644161","data":{"timestamp":" 947024644161"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" fe9e3dd9-7e0c-413b-82b6-72f0f3ec26e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PACHA"," userResponse":" PACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024645022","data":{"timestamp":" 947024645021"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" fe9e3dd9-7e0c-413b-82b6-72f0f3ec26e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENZAKE"," userResponse":" MWENZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024646221","data":{"timestamp":" 947024646221"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" fe9e3dd9-7e0c-413b-82b6-72f0f3ec26e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEITWA"," userResponse":" ALIYEITWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024647155","data":{"timestamp":" 947024647155"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" fe9e3dd9-7e0c-413b-82b6-72f0f3ec26e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DEMAZANE"," userResponse":" DEMAZANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024653084","data":{"timestamp":" 947024653083"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" fe9e3dd9-7e0c-413b-82b6-72f0f3ec26e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024653176","data":{"timestamp":" 947024653175"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" fe9e3dd9-7e0c-413b-82b6-72f0f3ec26e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DEMAZANE"," userResponse":" DEMAZANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024659579","data":{"timestamp":" 947024659578"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" fe9e3dd9-7e0c-413b-82b6-72f0f3ec26e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024666909","data":{"timestamp":" 947024666909"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" fe9e3dd9-7e0c-413b-82b6-72f0f3ec26e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024673014","data":{"timestamp":" 947024673013"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" fe9e3dd9-7e0c-413b-82b6-72f0f3ec26e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024834331","data":{"timestamp":" 947024834331"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" fe9e3dd9-7e0c-413b-82b6-72f0f3ec26e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024834393","data":{"timestamp":" 947024834393"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 14f16d12-ff11-431f-921d-0d28c9416d14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wachanga waliitwa Pop Mop na Pip."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIP"," userResponse":" PIP"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024841425","data":{"timestamp":" 947024841425"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 14f16d12-ff11-431f-921d-0d28c9416d14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wachanga waliitwa Pop Mop na Pip."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024849377","data":{"timestamp":" 947024849377"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 14f16d12-ff11-431f-921d-0d28c9416d14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wachanga waliitwa Pop Mop na Pip."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024859415","data":{"timestamp":" 947024859415"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 9b9fdde1-8d1f-403e-b41a-98a8e92993ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SABUNI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABUNI"," userResponse":" SABUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024868986","data":{"timestamp":" 947024868986"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 9b9fdde1-8d1f-403e-b41a-98a8e92993ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SABUNI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABUNI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024870599","data":{"timestamp":" 947024870599"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 9b9fdde1-8d1f-403e-b41a-98a8e92993ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SAHANI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAHANI"," userResponse":" SAHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024877829","data":{"timestamp":" 947024877829"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 9b9fdde1-8d1f-403e-b41a-98a8e92993ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SAHANI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAHANI"," userResponse":" SAHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024879451","data":{"timestamp":" 947024879451"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 9b9fdde1-8d1f-403e-b41a-98a8e92993ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SUFURIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUFURIA"," userResponse":" SUFURIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024884304","data":{"timestamp":" 947024884304"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 9b9fdde1-8d1f-403e-b41a-98a8e92993ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SUFURIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUFURIA"," userResponse":" SUFURIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024885878","data":{"timestamp":" 947024885877"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 9b9fdde1-8d1f-403e-b41a-98a8e92993ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SAMAKI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAKI"," userResponse":" SAMAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024888903","data":{"timestamp":" 947024888903"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 9b9fdde1-8d1f-403e-b41a-98a8e92993ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SAMAKI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAKI"," userResponse":" SAMAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024890522","data":{"timestamp":" 947024890522"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 9b9fdde1-8d1f-403e-b41a-98a8e92993ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SIMAMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMAMA"," userResponse":" SIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024893738","data":{"timestamp":" 947024893737"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 9b9fdde1-8d1f-403e-b41a-98a8e92993ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SIMAMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMAMA"," userResponse":" SIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024895284","data":{"timestamp":" 947024895284"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 9b9fdde1-8d1f-403e-b41a-98a8e92993ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SHANGAZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGAZI"," userResponse":" SHANGAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024902234","data":{"timestamp":" 947024902234"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 9b9fdde1-8d1f-403e-b41a-98a8e92993ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SHANGAZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGAZI"," userResponse":" SHANGAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024903869","data":{"timestamp":" 947024903868"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 9b9fdde1-8d1f-403e-b41a-98a8e92993ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SUNGURA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024907365","data":{"timestamp":" 947024907365"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 9b9fdde1-8d1f-403e-b41a-98a8e92993ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SUNGURA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024908931","data":{"timestamp":" 947024908931"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 9b9fdde1-8d1f-403e-b41a-98a8e92993ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SIKIO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" SIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024914061","data":{"timestamp":" 947024914061"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 9b9fdde1-8d1f-403e-b41a-98a8e92993ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SIKIO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" SIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024915617","data":{"timestamp":" 947024915617"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 9b9fdde1-8d1f-403e-b41a-98a8e92993ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SWALA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SWALA"," userResponse":" SWALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024918317","data":{"timestamp":" 947024918316"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 9b9fdde1-8d1f-403e-b41a-98a8e92993ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SWALA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SWALA"," userResponse":" SWALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024919877","data":{"timestamp":" 947024919877"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 9b9fdde1-8d1f-403e-b41a-98a8e92993ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAA"," userResponse":" SAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024922303","data":{"timestamp":" 947024922303"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 9b9fdde1-8d1f-403e-b41a-98a8e92993ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAA"," userResponse":" SAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024923863","data":{"timestamp":" 947024923862"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 9b9fdde1-8d1f-403e-b41a-98a8e92993ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SIMBA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024926332","data":{"timestamp":" 947024926332"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 9b9fdde1-8d1f-403e-b41a-98a8e92993ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SIMBA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024928344","data":{"timestamp":" 947024928344"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 9b9fdde1-8d1f-403e-b41a-98a8e92993ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" SIMBA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947024928503","data":{"timestamp":" 947024928503"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 9b9fdde1-8d1f-403e-b41a-98a8e92993ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SIMBA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025020245","data":{"timestamp":" 947025020245"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 9b9fdde1-8d1f-403e-b41a-98a8e92993ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" SIMBA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025020389","data":{"timestamp":" 947025020389"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 1cfbfc61-c4e0-4949-b9ae-0e62f101be1e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKUKIONA"," userResponse":" SIKUKIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025056950","data":{"timestamp":" 947025056949"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 1cfbfc61-c4e0-4949-b9ae-0e62f101be1e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025057020","data":{"timestamp":" 947025057020"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 0ace0c52-a81d-402d-bc72-6d4bddf9594c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKUKIONA"," userResponse":" SIKUKIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025183741","data":{"timestamp":" 947025183741"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" c6c8d1ba-3251-4e41-97c7-592474bcdb88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKUKIONA"," userResponse":" SIKUKIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025197471","data":{"timestamp":" 947025197470"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" c6c8d1ba-3251-4e41-97c7-592474bcdb88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025206589","data":{"timestamp":" 947025206589"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" c6c8d1ba-3251-4e41-97c7-592474bcdb88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025216787","data":{"timestamp":" 947025216786"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" c6c8d1ba-3251-4e41-97c7-592474bcdb88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025229055","data":{"timestamp":" 947025229054"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" c6c8d1ba-3251-4e41-97c7-592474bcdb88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025268032","data":{"timestamp":" 947025268032"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" c6c8d1ba-3251-4e41-97c7-592474bcdb88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025268162","data":{"timestamp":" 947025268162"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 38b3dd50-a0b6-40d5-a4a4-a28b5087e46a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DEMAZANE"," userResponse":" DEMAZANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025277282","data":{"timestamp":" 947025277282"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 38b3dd50-a0b6-40d5-a4a4-a28b5087e46a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025285117","data":{"timestamp":" 947025285116"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 38b3dd50-a0b6-40d5-a4a4-a28b5087e46a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025292033","data":{"timestamp":" 947025292032"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 38b3dd50-a0b6-40d5-a4a4-a28b5087e46a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025306609","data":{"timestamp":" 947025306609"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 38b3dd50-a0b6-40d5-a4a4-a28b5087e46a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025315910","data":{"timestamp":" 947025315909"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 38b3dd50-a0b6-40d5-a4a4-a28b5087e46a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025329310","data":{"timestamp":" 947025329310"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 38b3dd50-a0b6-40d5-a4a4-a28b5087e46a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025338394","data":{"timestamp":" 947025338393"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 38b3dd50-a0b6-40d5-a4a4-a28b5087e46a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025350255","data":{"timestamp":" 947025350255"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 38b3dd50-a0b6-40d5-a4a4-a28b5087e46a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025377218","data":{"timestamp":" 947025377217"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 38b3dd50-a0b6-40d5-a4a4-a28b5087e46a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025390754","data":{"timestamp":" 947025390754"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 38b3dd50-a0b6-40d5-a4a4-a28b5087e46a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025405538","data":{"timestamp":" 947025405536"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 38b3dd50-a0b6-40d5-a4a4-a28b5087e46a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025412636","data":{"timestamp":" 947025412635"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 38b3dd50-a0b6-40d5-a4a4-a28b5087e46a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025420005","data":{"timestamp":" 947025420004"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 38b3dd50-a0b6-40d5-a4a4-a28b5087e46a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025431350","data":{"timestamp":" 947025431350"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 38b3dd50-a0b6-40d5-a4a4-a28b5087e46a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025445589","data":{"timestamp":" 947025445588"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 38b3dd50-a0b6-40d5-a4a4-a28b5087e46a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025461611","data":{"timestamp":" 947025461611"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 38b3dd50-a0b6-40d5-a4a4-a28b5087e46a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025477270","data":{"timestamp":" 947025477270"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" c3d1f6de-2da2-4072-bce8-31e9e9ad6e9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TWIGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWIGA"," userResponse":" TWIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025481876","data":{"timestamp":" 947025481875"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" c3d1f6de-2da2-4072-bce8-31e9e9ad6e9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TWIGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWIGA"," userResponse":" TWIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025483527","data":{"timestamp":" 947025483527"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" c3d1f6de-2da2-4072-bce8-31e9e9ad6e9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TEMBO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025488642","data":{"timestamp":" 947025488642"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" c3d1f6de-2da2-4072-bce8-31e9e9ad6e9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TEMBO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025490209","data":{"timestamp":" 947025490209"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" c3d1f6de-2da2-4072-bce8-31e9e9ad6e9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025494666","data":{"timestamp":" 947025494666"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" c3d1f6de-2da2-4072-bce8-31e9e9ad6e9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025496232","data":{"timestamp":" 947025496232"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" c3d1f6de-2da2-4072-bce8-31e9e9ad6e9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TANO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025496876","data":{"timestamp":" 947025496875"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" c3d1f6de-2da2-4072-bce8-31e9e9ad6e9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" TANO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025497308","data":{"timestamp":" 947025497308"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" c3d1f6de-2da2-4072-bce8-31e9e9ad6e9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TANO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025508750","data":{"timestamp":" 947025508750"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" c3d1f6de-2da2-4072-bce8-31e9e9ad6e9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" TANO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.63","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025517606","data":{"timestamp":" 947025517606"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" c3d1f6de-2da2-4072-bce8-31e9e9ad6e9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" TANO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025541817","data":{"timestamp":" 947025541817"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" c3d1f6de-2da2-4072-bce8-31e9e9ad6e9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" TANO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025542067","data":{"timestamp":" 947025542067"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" e7664e63-78bc-41e8-aa34-190dc22a9eed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLANGO"," userResponse":" MLANGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025550241","data":{"timestamp":" 947025550241"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" e7664e63-78bc-41e8-aa34-190dc22a9eed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-1..20.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025566513","data":{"timestamp":" 947025566512"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" b659cc5f-c223-49f3-9a49-4d63bdc2eb22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-1..20.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-1..20.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025567826","data":{"timestamp":" 947025567826"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" b659cc5f-c223-49f3-9a49-4d63bdc2eb22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-1..20.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-1..20.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025569366","data":{"timestamp":" 947025569366"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" b659cc5f-c223-49f3-9a49-4d63bdc2eb22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-1..20.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-1..20.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025584624","data":{"timestamp":" 947025584624"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" b659cc5f-c223-49f3-9a49-4d63bdc2eb22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-1..20.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-1..20.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025611765","data":{"timestamp":" 947025611765"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" b659cc5f-c223-49f3-9a49-4d63bdc2eb22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-1..20.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-1..20.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025619010","data":{"timestamp":" 947025619010"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" b659cc5f-c223-49f3-9a49-4d63bdc2eb22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-1..20.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-1..20.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025625907","data":{"timestamp":" 947025625906"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" b659cc5f-c223-49f3-9a49-4d63bdc2eb22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-1..20.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-1..20.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025626643","data":{"timestamp":" 947025626642"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" b659cc5f-c223-49f3-9a49-4d63bdc2eb22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-1..20.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-1..20.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025635479","data":{"timestamp":" 947025635479"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" b659cc5f-c223-49f3-9a49-4d63bdc2eb22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-1..20.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-1..20.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025636011","data":{"timestamp":" 947025636011"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" b659cc5f-c223-49f3-9a49-4d63bdc2eb22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-1..20.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025646739","data":{"timestamp":" 947025646739"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" dc85a804-6a18-4864-a494-aeb03086b7dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025647114","data":{"timestamp":" 947025647114"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" dc85a804-6a18-4864-a494-aeb03086b7dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025647600","data":{"timestamp":" 947025647600"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" dc85a804-6a18-4864-a494-aeb03086b7dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025647946","data":{"timestamp":" 947025647946"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" dc85a804-6a18-4864-a494-aeb03086b7dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025648352","data":{"timestamp":" 947025648352"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" dc85a804-6a18-4864-a494-aeb03086b7dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025648826","data":{"timestamp":" 947025648826"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" dc85a804-6a18-4864-a494-aeb03086b7dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025649050","data":{"timestamp":" 947025649050"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" dc85a804-6a18-4864-a494-aeb03086b7dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025652286","data":{"timestamp":" 947025652286"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" dc85a804-6a18-4864-a494-aeb03086b7dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025652320","data":{"timestamp":" 947025652320"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" dc85a804-6a18-4864-a494-aeb03086b7dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025653039","data":{"timestamp":" 947025653039"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" dc85a804-6a18-4864-a494-aeb03086b7dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025653439","data":{"timestamp":" 947025653438"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" dc85a804-6a18-4864-a494-aeb03086b7dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025653738","data":{"timestamp":" 947025653737"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" dc85a804-6a18-4864-a494-aeb03086b7dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025653949","data":{"timestamp":" 947025653949"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" dc85a804-6a18-4864-a494-aeb03086b7dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025654147","data":{"timestamp":" 947025654147"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" dc85a804-6a18-4864-a494-aeb03086b7dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025654469","data":{"timestamp":" 947025654468"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" dc85a804-6a18-4864-a494-aeb03086b7dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025654697","data":{"timestamp":" 947025654697"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" dc85a804-6a18-4864-a494-aeb03086b7dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025656983","data":{"timestamp":" 947025656982"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" dc85a804-6a18-4864-a494-aeb03086b7dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025657205","data":{"timestamp":" 947025657205"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" dc85a804-6a18-4864-a494-aeb03086b7dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025667613","data":{"timestamp":" 947025667613"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" db8495f4-4751-41d0-a13d-74d3cd619ac7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025667838","data":{"timestamp":" 947025667838"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" db8495f4-4751-41d0-a13d-74d3cd619ac7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025668802","data":{"timestamp":" 947025668802"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" db8495f4-4751-41d0-a13d-74d3cd619ac7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025670077","data":{"timestamp":" 947025670076"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" db8495f4-4751-41d0-a13d-74d3cd619ac7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025672994","data":{"timestamp":" 947025672994"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" db8495f4-4751-41d0-a13d-74d3cd619ac7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025673259","data":{"timestamp":" 947025673259"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" db8495f4-4751-41d0-a13d-74d3cd619ac7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_22"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025673447","data":{"timestamp":" 947025673447"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" db8495f4-4751-41d0-a13d-74d3cd619ac7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:T..T.all.10.rand.say.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025683280","data":{"timestamp":" 947025683280"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" db8495f4-4751-41d0-a13d-74d3cd619ac7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_22"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025692027","data":{"timestamp":" 947025692026"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" db8495f4-4751-41d0-a13d-74d3cd619ac7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_22"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025703469","data":{"timestamp":" 947025703468"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" db8495f4-4751-41d0-a13d-74d3cd619ac7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_22"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025717004","data":{"timestamp":" 947025717004"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Ndovu na Sungura walikuwa marafiki wakubwa sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025717559","data":{"timestamp":" 947025717559"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Ndovu na Sungura walikuwa marafiki wakubwa sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025717768","data":{"timestamp":" 947025717768"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Ndovu na Sungura walikuwa marafiki wakubwa sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025718156","data":{"timestamp":" 947025718156"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Ndovu na Sungura walikuwa marafiki wakubwa sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025719176","data":{"timestamp":" 947025719176"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Ndovu na Sungura walikuwa marafiki wakubwa sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOVU"," userResponse":" NDOVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025719334","data":{"timestamp":" 947025719334"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Ndovu na Sungura walikuwa marafiki wakubwa sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025719980","data":{"timestamp":" 947025719980"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Ndovu na Sungura walikuwa marafiki wakubwa sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025720660","data":{"timestamp":" 947025720660"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Ndovu na Sungura walikuwa marafiki wakubwa sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025721363","data":{"timestamp":" 947025721362"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Ndovu na Sungura walikuwa marafiki wakubwa sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARAFIKI"," userResponse":" MARAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025722173","data":{"timestamp":" 947025722173"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Ndovu na Sungura walikuwa marafiki wakubwa sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKUBWA"," userResponse":" WAKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025722654","data":{"timestamp":" 947025722654"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Ndovu na Sungura walikuwa marafiki wakubwa sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025725225","data":{"timestamp":" 947025725225"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na ngamia ng'ombe na kondoo wengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025725452","data":{"timestamp":" 947025725452"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na ngamia ng'ombe na kondoo wengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025726397","data":{"timestamp":" 947025726397"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na ngamia ng'ombe na kondoo wengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGAMIA"," userResponse":" NGAMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025727493","data":{"timestamp":" 947025727493"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na ngamia ng'ombe na kondoo wengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025727510","data":{"timestamp":" 947025727510"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na ngamia ng'ombe na kondoo wengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025727886","data":{"timestamp":" 947025727886"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na ngamia ng'ombe na kondoo wengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025728305","data":{"timestamp":" 947025728305"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na ngamia ng'ombe na kondoo wengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KONDOO"," userResponse":" KONDOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025728993","data":{"timestamp":" 947025728993"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na ngamia ng'ombe na kondoo wengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGI"," userResponse":" WENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025732257","data":{"timestamp":" 947025732257"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walilisha wanyama hao katika bonde la Kingilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALILISHA"," userResponse":" WALILISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025732863","data":{"timestamp":" 947025732862"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walilisha wanyama hao katika bonde la Kingilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025733531","data":{"timestamp":" 947025733531"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walilisha wanyama hao katika bonde la Kingilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAO"," userResponse":" HAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025734344","data":{"timestamp":" 947025734344"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walilisha wanyama hao katika bonde la Kingilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025734788","data":{"timestamp":" 947025734788"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walilisha wanyama hao katika bonde la Kingilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BONDE"," userResponse":" BONDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025734975","data":{"timestamp":" 947025734975"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walilisha wanyama hao katika bonde la Kingilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025735672","data":{"timestamp":" 947025735672"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walilisha wanyama hao katika bonde la Kingilo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINGILO"," userResponse":" KINGILO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025738188","data":{"timestamp":" 947025738188"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine waliwapeleka wanyama milimani ambako kulikuwa na nyasi na maji kwa wingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025738938","data":{"timestamp":" 947025738938"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine waliwapeleka wanyama milimani ambako kulikuwa na nyasi na maji kwa wingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025740367","data":{"timestamp":" 947025740367"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine waliwapeleka wanyama milimani ambako kulikuwa na nyasi na maji kwa wingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIWAPELEKA"," userResponse":" WALIWAPELEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025741085","data":{"timestamp":" 947025741085"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine waliwapeleka wanyama milimani ambako kulikuwa na nyasi na maji kwa wingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025742214","data":{"timestamp":" 947025742214"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine waliwapeleka wanyama milimani ambako kulikuwa na nyasi na maji kwa wingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MILIMANI"," userResponse":" MILIMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025743079","data":{"timestamp":" 947025743079"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine waliwapeleka wanyama milimani ambako kulikuwa na nyasi na maji kwa wingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAKO"," userResponse":" AMBAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025743786","data":{"timestamp":" 947025743786"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine waliwapeleka wanyama milimani ambako kulikuwa na nyasi na maji kwa wingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" KULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025743983","data":{"timestamp":" 947025743983"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine waliwapeleka wanyama milimani ambako kulikuwa na nyasi na maji kwa wingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025744789","data":{"timestamp":" 947025744789"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine waliwapeleka wanyama milimani ambako kulikuwa na nyasi na maji kwa wingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYASI"," userResponse":" NYASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025745157","data":{"timestamp":" 947025745157"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine waliwapeleka wanyama milimani ambako kulikuwa na nyasi na maji kwa wingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025745651","data":{"timestamp":" 947025745651"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine waliwapeleka wanyama milimani ambako kulikuwa na nyasi na maji kwa wingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025745970","data":{"timestamp":" 947025745969"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine waliwapeleka wanyama milimani ambako kulikuwa na nyasi na maji kwa wingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025746538","data":{"timestamp":" 947025746538"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine waliwapeleka wanyama milimani ambako kulikuwa na nyasi na maji kwa wingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WINGI"," userResponse":" WINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025749587","data":{"timestamp":" 947025749587"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama walipokula Sungura na Ndovu walicheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025750683","data":{"timestamp":" 947025750683"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama walipokula Sungura na Ndovu walicheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOKULA"," userResponse":" WALIPOKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025751575","data":{"timestamp":" 947025751575"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama walipokula Sungura na Ndovu walicheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025751771","data":{"timestamp":" 947025751770"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama walipokula Sungura na Ndovu walicheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025752215","data":{"timestamp":" 947025752215"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama walipokula Sungura na Ndovu walicheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOVU"," userResponse":" NDOVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025753188","data":{"timestamp":" 947025753188"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama walipokula Sungura na Ndovu walicheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALICHEZA"," userResponse":" WALICHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025756246","data":{"timestamp":" 947025756246"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifurahia sana kucheza mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIFURAHIA"," userResponse":" WALIFURAHIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025757062","data":{"timestamp":" 947025757061"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifurahia sana kucheza mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025757965","data":{"timestamp":" 947025757965"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifurahia sana kucheza mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZA"," userResponse":" KUCHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025758682","data":{"timestamp":" 947025758682"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifurahia sana kucheza mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPIRA"," userResponse":" MPIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025758907","data":{"timestamp":" 947025758907"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifurahia sana kucheza mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025759394","data":{"timestamp":" 947025759394"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifurahia sana kucheza mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" MIGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025762331","data":{"timestamp":" 947025762330"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila walipocheza Ndovu aliingiza mabao mengi kuliko Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025763526","data":{"timestamp":" 947025763526"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila walipocheza Ndovu aliingiza mabao mengi kuliko Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOCHEZA"," userResponse":" WALIPOCHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025764302","data":{"timestamp":" 947025764302"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila walipocheza Ndovu aliingiza mabao mengi kuliko Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOVU"," userResponse":" NDOVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025765370","data":{"timestamp":" 947025765370"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila walipocheza Ndovu aliingiza mabao mengi kuliko Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIINGIZA"," userResponse":" ALIINGIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025766025","data":{"timestamp":" 947025766025"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila walipocheza Ndovu aliingiza mabao mengi kuliko Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MABAO"," userResponse":" MABAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025766658","data":{"timestamp":" 947025766658"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila walipocheza Ndovu aliingiza mabao mengi kuliko Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENGI"," userResponse":" MENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025767174","data":{"timestamp":" 947025767173"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila walipocheza Ndovu aliingiza mabao mengi kuliko Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKO"," userResponse":" KULIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025767865","data":{"timestamp":" 947025767864"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila walipocheza Ndovu aliingiza mabao mengi kuliko Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025770559","data":{"timestamp":" 947025770559"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hili lilimkasirisha Sungura mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" HILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025771704","data":{"timestamp":" 947025771704"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hili lilimkasirisha Sungura mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIMKASIRISHA"," userResponse":" LILIMKASIRISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025772357","data":{"timestamp":" 947025772356"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hili lilimkasirisha Sungura mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025773083","data":{"timestamp":" 947025773082"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hili lilimkasirisha Sungura mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNO"," userResponse":" MNO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025776200","data":{"timestamp":" 947025776200"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Sungura alimuuliza Ndovu Nini kinachokuwezesha kuwa mwingizaji goli maarufu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025776848","data":{"timestamp":" 947025776847"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Sungura alimuuliza Ndovu Nini kinachokuwezesha kuwa mwingizaji goli maarufu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025777660","data":{"timestamp":" 947025777660"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Sungura alimuuliza Ndovu Nini kinachokuwezesha kuwa mwingizaji goli maarufu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025778659","data":{"timestamp":" 947025778659"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Sungura alimuuliza Ndovu Nini kinachokuwezesha kuwa mwingizaji goli maarufu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMUULIZA"," userResponse":" ALIMUULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025779180","data":{"timestamp":" 947025779176"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Sungura alimuuliza Ndovu Nini kinachokuwezesha kuwa mwingizaji goli maarufu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOVU"," userResponse":" NDOVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025780309","data":{"timestamp":" 947025780308"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Sungura alimuuliza Ndovu Nini kinachokuwezesha kuwa mwingizaji goli maarufu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025781906","data":{"timestamp":" 947025781905"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Sungura alimuuliza Ndovu Nini kinachokuwezesha kuwa mwingizaji goli maarufu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINACHOKUWEZESHA"," userResponse":" KINACHOKUWEZESHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025782587","data":{"timestamp":" 947025782586"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Sungura alimuuliza Ndovu Nini kinachokuwezesha kuwa mwingizaji goli maarufu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025783486","data":{"timestamp":" 947025783485"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Sungura alimuuliza Ndovu Nini kinachokuwezesha kuwa mwingizaji goli maarufu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGIZAJI"," userResponse":" MWINGIZAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025783932","data":{"timestamp":" 947025783932"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Sungura alimuuliza Ndovu Nini kinachokuwezesha kuwa mwingizaji goli maarufu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOLI"," userResponse":" GOLI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025784922","data":{"timestamp":" 947025784922"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Sungura alimuuliza Ndovu Nini kinachokuwezesha kuwa mwingizaji goli maarufu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAARUFU"," userResponse":" MAARUFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025787344","data":{"timestamp":" 947025787343"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alijibu kwa haraka Miguu yangu minene."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOVU"," userResponse":" NDOVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025787912","data":{"timestamp":" 947025787912"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alijibu kwa haraka Miguu yangu minene."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIBU"," userResponse":" ALIJIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025788256","data":{"timestamp":" 947025788256"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alijibu kwa haraka Miguu yangu minene."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025788844","data":{"timestamp":" 947025788844"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alijibu kwa haraka Miguu yangu minene."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" HARAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025789770","data":{"timestamp":" 947025789770"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alijibu kwa haraka Miguu yangu minene."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" MIGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025790262","data":{"timestamp":" 947025790261"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alijibu kwa haraka Miguu yangu minene."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025790883","data":{"timestamp":" 947025790883"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alijibu kwa haraka Miguu yangu minene."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MINENE"," userResponse":" MINENE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025793930","data":{"timestamp":" 947025793930"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sungura alipendekeza wawe na mashindano ya mbio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025795030","data":{"timestamp":" 947025795030"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sungura alipendekeza wawe na mashindano ya mbio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOFUATA"," userResponse":" ILIYOFUATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025796076","data":{"timestamp":" 947025796076"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sungura alipendekeza wawe na mashindano ya mbio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025797437","data":{"timestamp":" 947025797437"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sungura alipendekeza wawe na mashindano ya mbio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPENDEKEZA"," userResponse":" ALIPENDEKEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025798074","data":{"timestamp":" 947025798074"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sungura alipendekeza wawe na mashindano ya mbio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAWE"," userResponse":" WAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025798281","data":{"timestamp":" 947025798281"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sungura alipendekeza wawe na mashindano ya mbio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025799119","data":{"timestamp":" 947025799119"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sungura alipendekeza wawe na mashindano ya mbio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHINDANO"," userResponse":" MASHINDANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025799331","data":{"timestamp":" 947025799330"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sungura alipendekeza wawe na mashindano ya mbio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025799817","data":{"timestamp":" 947025799816"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sungura alipendekeza wawe na mashindano ya mbio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBIO"," userResponse":" MBIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025802221","data":{"timestamp":" 947025802221"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alikubali na wakaanza mbio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOVU"," userResponse":" NDOVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025803506","data":{"timestamp":" 947025803506"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alikubali na wakaanza mbio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUBALI"," userResponse":" ALIKUBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025803905","data":{"timestamp":" 947025803904"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alikubali na wakaanza mbio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025804732","data":{"timestamp":" 947025804732"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alikubali na wakaanza mbio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAANZA"," userResponse":" WAKAANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025805197","data":{"timestamp":" 947025805197"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alikubali na wakaanza mbio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBIO"," userResponse":" MBIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025808477","data":{"timestamp":" 947025808477"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alishinda mbio zote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025809393","data":{"timestamp":" 947025809393"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alishinda mbio zote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISHINDA"," userResponse":" ALISHINDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025809809","data":{"timestamp":" 947025809809"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alishinda mbio zote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBIO"," userResponse":" MBIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025810496","data":{"timestamp":" 947025810496"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alishinda mbio zote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZOTE"," userResponse":" ZOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025813038","data":{"timestamp":" 947025813038"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alikasirika kwa sababu hakuwahi kushindwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOVU"," userResponse":" NDOVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025814350","data":{"timestamp":" 947025814350"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alikasirika kwa sababu hakuwahi kushindwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKASIRIKA"," userResponse":" ALIKASIRIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025814543","data":{"timestamp":" 947025814543"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alikasirika kwa sababu hakuwahi kushindwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025815039","data":{"timestamp":" 947025815039"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alikasirika kwa sababu hakuwahi kushindwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" SABABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025816178","data":{"timestamp":" 947025816177"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alikasirika kwa sababu hakuwahi kushindwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWAHI"," userResponse":" HAKUWAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025816859","data":{"timestamp":" 947025816859"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alikasirika kwa sababu hakuwahi kushindwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSHINDWA"," userResponse":" KUSHINDWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025818849","data":{"timestamp":" 947025818848"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alimuuliza Sungura Nini kinachokuwezesha kuwa mkimbiaji maarufu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025819409","data":{"timestamp":" 947025819409"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alimuuliza Sungura Nini kinachokuwezesha kuwa mkimbiaji maarufu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025820315","data":{"timestamp":" 947025820315"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alimuuliza Sungura Nini kinachokuwezesha kuwa mkimbiaji maarufu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMUULIZA"," userResponse":" ALIMUULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025820982","data":{"timestamp":" 947025820982"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alimuuliza Sungura Nini kinachokuwezesha kuwa mkimbiaji maarufu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025821942","data":{"timestamp":" 947025821942"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alimuuliza Sungura Nini kinachokuwezesha kuwa mkimbiaji maarufu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025823228","data":{"timestamp":" 947025823227"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alimuuliza Sungura Nini kinachokuwezesha kuwa mkimbiaji maarufu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINACHOKUWEZESHA"," userResponse":" KINACHOKUWEZESHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025823586","data":{"timestamp":" 947025823585"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alimuuliza Sungura Nini kinachokuwezesha kuwa mkimbiaji maarufu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025824474","data":{"timestamp":" 947025824474"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alimuuliza Sungura Nini kinachokuwezesha kuwa mkimbiaji maarufu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKIMBIAJI"," userResponse":" MKIMBIAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025825500","data":{"timestamp":" 947025825499"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alimuuliza Sungura Nini kinachokuwezesha kuwa mkimbiaji maarufu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAARUFU"," userResponse":" MAARUFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025828262","data":{"timestamp":" 947025828262"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alijibu Miguu yangu myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025829139","data":{"timestamp":" 947025829139"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alijibu Miguu yangu myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIBU"," userResponse":" ALIJIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025829984","data":{"timestamp":" 947025829984"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alijibu Miguu yangu myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" MIGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025830680","data":{"timestamp":" 947025830680"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alijibu Miguu yangu myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025831498","data":{"timestamp":" 947025831497"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alijibu Miguu yangu myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MYEMBAMBA"," userResponse":" MYEMBAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025834443","data":{"timestamp":" 947025834443"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila kuwaza zaidi Ndovu aliuliza kile angelifanya ili miguu yake iwe myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025835058","data":{"timestamp":" 947025835058"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila kuwaza zaidi Ndovu aliuliza kile angelifanya ili miguu yake iwe myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAZA"," userResponse":" KUWAZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025835835","data":{"timestamp":" 947025835835"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila kuwaza zaidi Ndovu aliuliza kile angelifanya ili miguu yake iwe myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025836591","data":{"timestamp":" 947025836591"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila kuwaza zaidi Ndovu aliuliza kile angelifanya ili miguu yake iwe myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOVU"," userResponse":" NDOVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025837629","data":{"timestamp":" 947025837628"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila kuwaza zaidi Ndovu aliuliza kile angelifanya ili miguu yake iwe myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIULIZA"," userResponse":" ALIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025838284","data":{"timestamp":" 947025838284"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila kuwaza zaidi Ndovu aliuliza kile angelifanya ili miguu yake iwe myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILE"," userResponse":" KILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025839392","data":{"timestamp":" 947025839392"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila kuwaza zaidi Ndovu aliuliza kile angelifanya ili miguu yake iwe myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGELIFANYA"," userResponse":" ANGELIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025840061","data":{"timestamp":" 947025840061"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila kuwaza zaidi Ndovu aliuliza kile angelifanya ili miguu yake iwe myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" ILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025840602","data":{"timestamp":" 947025840602"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila kuwaza zaidi Ndovu aliuliza kile angelifanya ili miguu yake iwe myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" MIGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025840960","data":{"timestamp":" 947025840960"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila kuwaza zaidi Ndovu aliuliza kile angelifanya ili miguu yake iwe myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025841453","data":{"timestamp":" 947025841453"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila kuwaza zaidi Ndovu aliuliza kile angelifanya ili miguu yake iwe myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IWE"," userResponse":" IWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025842434","data":{"timestamp":" 947025842433"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila kuwaza zaidi Ndovu aliuliza kile angelifanya ili miguu yake iwe myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MYEMBAMBA"," userResponse":" MYEMBAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025845097","data":{"timestamp":" 947025845096"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alisema Ni rahisi nitakuonyesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025845952","data":{"timestamp":" 947025845952"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alisema Ni rahisi nitakuonyesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025846630","data":{"timestamp":" 947025846630"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alisema Ni rahisi nitakuonyesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025847287","data":{"timestamp":" 947025847287"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alisema Ni rahisi nitakuonyesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHISI"," userResponse":" RAHISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025848872","data":{"timestamp":" 947025848872"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alisema Ni rahisi nitakuonyesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAKUONYESHA"," userResponse":" NITAKUONYESHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025851549","data":{"timestamp":" 947025851549"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafuta kuni na ukoke moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFUTA"," userResponse":" TAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025852108","data":{"timestamp":" 947025852108"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafuta kuni na ukoke moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNI"," userResponse":" KUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025852584","data":{"timestamp":" 947025852584"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafuta kuni na ukoke moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025853020","data":{"timestamp":" 947025853020"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafuta kuni na ukoke moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKOKE"," userResponse":" UKOKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025853583","data":{"timestamp":" 947025853583"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafuta kuni na ukoke moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025856399","data":{"timestamp":" 947025856398"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alikusanya kuni na kukoka moto mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOVU"," userResponse":" NDOVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025857651","data":{"timestamp":" 947025857651"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alikusanya kuni na kukoka moto mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUSANYA"," userResponse":" ALIKUSANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025858327","data":{"timestamp":" 947025858327"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alikusanya kuni na kukoka moto mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNI"," userResponse":" KUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025858808","data":{"timestamp":" 947025858808"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alikusanya kuni na kukoka moto mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025859528","data":{"timestamp":" 947025859527"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alikusanya kuni na kukoka moto mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKOKA"," userResponse":" KUKOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025860055","data":{"timestamp":" 947025860055"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alikusanya kuni na kukoka moto mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025861154","data":{"timestamp":" 947025861154"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alikusanya kuni na kukoka moto mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBWA"," userResponse":" MKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025863727","data":{"timestamp":" 947025863726"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alisema Sasa iweke miguu yako motoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025864544","data":{"timestamp":" 947025864544"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alisema Sasa iweke miguu yako motoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025865591","data":{"timestamp":" 947025865591"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alisema Sasa iweke miguu yako motoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025866411","data":{"timestamp":" 947025866411"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alisema Sasa iweke miguu yako motoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IWEKE"," userResponse":" IWEKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025866961","data":{"timestamp":" 947025866961"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alisema Sasa iweke miguu yako motoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" MIGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025867452","data":{"timestamp":" 947025867452"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alisema Sasa iweke miguu yako motoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKO"," userResponse":" YAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025868130","data":{"timestamp":" 947025868130"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alisema Sasa iweke miguu yako motoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTONI"," userResponse":" MOTONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025870668","data":{"timestamp":" 947025870668"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alisimama ndani ya moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOVU"," userResponse":" NDOVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025871555","data":{"timestamp":" 947025871554"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alisimama ndani ya moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISIMAMA"," userResponse":" ALISIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025872104","data":{"timestamp":" 947025872104"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alisimama ndani ya moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025872194","data":{"timestamp":" 947025872194"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alisimama ndani ya moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025872748","data":{"timestamp":" 947025872746"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alisimama ndani ya moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025875457","data":{"timestamp":" 947025875457"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nateketea!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPIGA"," userResponse":" ALIPIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025875939","data":{"timestamp":" 947025875939"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nateketea!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KELELE"," userResponse":" KELELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025877443","data":{"timestamp":" 947025877443"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nateketea!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NATEKETEA"," userResponse":" NATEKETEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025881282","data":{"timestamp":" 947025881281"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nateketea!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NATEKETEA"," userResponse":" NATEKETEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025884652","data":{"timestamp":" 947025884652"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alifurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025886917","data":{"timestamp":" 947025886917"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alifurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFURAHI"," userResponse":" ALIFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025890154","data":{"timestamp":" 947025890153"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimhimiza Ndovu aendelea hivyo hivyo maanake hivyo tu ndivyo miguu yake ingelikuwa myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMHIMIZA"," userResponse":" ALIMHIMIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025890751","data":{"timestamp":" 947025890751"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimhimiza Ndovu aendelea hivyo hivyo maanake hivyo tu ndivyo miguu yake ingelikuwa myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOVU"," userResponse":" NDOVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025892088","data":{"timestamp":" 947025892088"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimhimiza Ndovu aendelea hivyo hivyo maanake hivyo tu ndivyo miguu yake ingelikuwa myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AENDELEA"," userResponse":" AENDELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025892984","data":{"timestamp":" 947025892984"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimhimiza Ndovu aendelea hivyo hivyo maanake hivyo tu ndivyo miguu yake ingelikuwa myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025893721","data":{"timestamp":" 947025893721"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimhimiza Ndovu aendelea hivyo hivyo maanake hivyo tu ndivyo miguu yake ingelikuwa myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025894798","data":{"timestamp":" 947025894798"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimhimiza Ndovu aendelea hivyo hivyo maanake hivyo tu ndivyo miguu yake ingelikuwa myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAANAKE"," userResponse":" MAANAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025895325","data":{"timestamp":" 947025895324"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimhimiza Ndovu aendelea hivyo hivyo maanake hivyo tu ndivyo miguu yake ingelikuwa myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025895502","data":{"timestamp":" 947025895501"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimhimiza Ndovu aendelea hivyo hivyo maanake hivyo tu ndivyo miguu yake ingelikuwa myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025896245","data":{"timestamp":" 947025896245"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimhimiza Ndovu aendelea hivyo hivyo maanake hivyo tu ndivyo miguu yake ingelikuwa myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIVYO"," userResponse":" NDIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025896773","data":{"timestamp":" 947025896773"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimhimiza Ndovu aendelea hivyo hivyo maanake hivyo tu ndivyo miguu yake ingelikuwa myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" MIGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025897318","data":{"timestamp":" 947025897318"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimhimiza Ndovu aendelea hivyo hivyo maanake hivyo tu ndivyo miguu yake ingelikuwa myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025898456","data":{"timestamp":" 947025898456"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimhimiza Ndovu aendelea hivyo hivyo maanake hivyo tu ndivyo miguu yake ingelikuwa myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INGELIKUWA"," userResponse":" INGELIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025899213","data":{"timestamp":" 947025899213"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimhimiza Ndovu aendelea hivyo hivyo maanake hivyo tu ndivyo miguu yake ingelikuwa myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MYEMBAMBA"," userResponse":" MYEMBAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025901762","data":{"timestamp":" 947025901762"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguu ya Ndovu ilijeruhiwa vibaya kwa hivyo aliondoka motoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" MIGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025902008","data":{"timestamp":" 947025902008"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguu ya Ndovu ilijeruhiwa vibaya kwa hivyo aliondoka motoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025902372","data":{"timestamp":" 947025902372"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguu ya Ndovu ilijeruhiwa vibaya kwa hivyo aliondoka motoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOVU"," userResponse":" NDOVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025904114","data":{"timestamp":" 947025904113"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguu ya Ndovu ilijeruhiwa vibaya kwa hivyo aliondoka motoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIJERUHIWA"," userResponse":" ILIJERUHIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025905347","data":{"timestamp":" 947025905346"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguu ya Ndovu ilijeruhiwa vibaya kwa hivyo aliondoka motoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIBAYA"," userResponse":" VIBAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025906005","data":{"timestamp":" 947025906005"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguu ya Ndovu ilijeruhiwa vibaya kwa hivyo aliondoka motoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025906532","data":{"timestamp":" 947025906532"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguu ya Ndovu ilijeruhiwa vibaya kwa hivyo aliondoka motoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025907430","data":{"timestamp":" 947025907430"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguu ya Ndovu ilijeruhiwa vibaya kwa hivyo aliondoka motoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONDOKA"," userResponse":" ALIONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025908147","data":{"timestamp":" 947025908147"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguu ya Ndovu ilijeruhiwa vibaya kwa hivyo aliondoka motoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTONI"," userResponse":" MOTONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025911073","data":{"timestamp":" 947025911073"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hangeweza kusimama kwa hivyo alilala chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HANGEWEZA"," userResponse":" HANGEWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025912037","data":{"timestamp":" 947025912037"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hangeweza kusimama kwa hivyo alilala chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSIMAMA"," userResponse":" KUSIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025912570","data":{"timestamp":" 947025912570"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hangeweza kusimama kwa hivyo alilala chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025913002","data":{"timestamp":" 947025913002"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hangeweza kusimama kwa hivyo alilala chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025913732","data":{"timestamp":" 947025913732"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hangeweza kusimama kwa hivyo alilala chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALILALA"," userResponse":" ALILALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025914253","data":{"timestamp":" 947025914253"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hangeweza kusimama kwa hivyo alilala chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025917339","data":{"timestamp":" 947025917339"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu aliketi kwa siku nyingi kabla kuweza kusimama kwa miguu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOVU"," userResponse":" NDOVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025918236","data":{"timestamp":" 947025918236"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu aliketi kwa siku nyingi kabla kuweza kusimama kwa miguu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKETI"," userResponse":" ALIKETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025918494","data":{"timestamp":" 947025918494"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu aliketi kwa siku nyingi kabla kuweza kusimama kwa miguu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025918954","data":{"timestamp":" 947025918954"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu aliketi kwa siku nyingi kabla kuweza kusimama kwa miguu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025919771","data":{"timestamp":" 947025919771"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu aliketi kwa siku nyingi kabla kuweza kusimama kwa miguu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGI"," userResponse":" NYINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025920431","data":{"timestamp":" 947025920431"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu aliketi kwa siku nyingi kabla kuweza kusimama kwa miguu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KABLA"," userResponse":" KABLA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025921016","data":{"timestamp":" 947025921016"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu aliketi kwa siku nyingi kabla kuweza kusimama kwa miguu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWEZA"," userResponse":" KUWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025921764","data":{"timestamp":" 947025921764"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu aliketi kwa siku nyingi kabla kuweza kusimama kwa miguu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSIMAMA"," userResponse":" KUSIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025921999","data":{"timestamp":" 947025921999"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu aliketi kwa siku nyingi kabla kuweza kusimama kwa miguu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025922646","data":{"timestamp":" 947025922646"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu aliketi kwa siku nyingi kabla kuweza kusimama kwa miguu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" MIGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025923014","data":{"timestamp":" 947025923014"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu aliketi kwa siku nyingi kabla kuweza kusimama kwa miguu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025926416","data":{"timestamp":" 947025926416"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye aliweza kuchechemea na kwenda nyumbani kwa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATIMAYE"," userResponse":" HATIMAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025927575","data":{"timestamp":" 947025927575"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye aliweza kuchechemea na kwenda nyumbani kwa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWEZA"," userResponse":" ALIWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025928696","data":{"timestamp":" 947025928696"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye aliweza kuchechemea na kwenda nyumbani kwa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHECHEMEA"," userResponse":" KUCHECHEMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025929147","data":{"timestamp":" 947025929147"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye aliweza kuchechemea na kwenda nyumbani kwa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025929589","data":{"timestamp":" 947025929589"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye aliweza kuchechemea na kwenda nyumbani kwa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025930216","data":{"timestamp":" 947025930216"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye aliweza kuchechemea na kwenda nyumbani kwa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025930455","data":{"timestamp":" 947025930455"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye aliweza kuchechemea na kwenda nyumbani kwa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025931336","data":{"timestamp":" 947025931336"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye aliweza kuchechemea na kwenda nyumbani kwa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025931601","data":{"timestamp":" 947025931601"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye aliweza kuchechemea na kwenda nyumbani kwa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025934741","data":{"timestamp":" 947025934741"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura na Ndovu si marafiki tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025934984","data":{"timestamp":" 947025934983"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura na Ndovu si marafiki tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025935510","data":{"timestamp":" 947025935510"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura na Ndovu si marafiki tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOVU"," userResponse":" NDOVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025936091","data":{"timestamp":" 947025936090"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura na Ndovu si marafiki tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SI"," userResponse":" SI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025937017","data":{"timestamp":" 947025937017"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura na Ndovu si marafiki tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARAFIKI"," userResponse":" MARAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025937723","data":{"timestamp":" 947025937723"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura na Ndovu si marafiki tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025940477","data":{"timestamp":" 947025940477"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Sungura na Ndovu si marafiki tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025940757","data":{"timestamp":" 947025940757"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura na Ndovu si marafiki tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025948696","data":{"timestamp":" 947025948696"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 134e2fe4-562b-490d-aaa2-0d72dd6c1afd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Sungura na Ndovu si marafiki tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025961510","data":{"timestamp":" 947025961510"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 624e487c-bf73-40d0-b6f3-d240c9e361ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Najua kuhesabu namba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAJUA"," userResponse":" NAJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025962585","data":{"timestamp":" 947025962585"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 624e487c-bf73-40d0-b6f3-d240c9e361ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Najua kuhesabu namba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUHESABU"," userResponse":" KUHESABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025963503","data":{"timestamp":" 947025963503"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 624e487c-bf73-40d0-b6f3-d240c9e361ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Najua kuhesabu namba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMBA"," userResponse":" NAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025967309","data":{"timestamp":" 947025967309"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 624e487c-bf73-40d0-b6f3-d240c9e361ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Moja mbili tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025967807","data":{"timestamp":" 947025967807"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 624e487c-bf73-40d0-b6f3-d240c9e361ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Moja mbili tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBILI"," userResponse":" MBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025968437","data":{"timestamp":" 947025968437"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 624e487c-bf73-40d0-b6f3-d240c9e361ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Moja mbili tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025971880","data":{"timestamp":" 947025971880"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 624e487c-bf73-40d0-b6f3-d240c9e361ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nne tano sita saba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NNE"," userResponse":" NNE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025972680","data":{"timestamp":" 947025972680"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 624e487c-bf73-40d0-b6f3-d240c9e361ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nne tano sita saba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025973073","data":{"timestamp":" 947025973073"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 624e487c-bf73-40d0-b6f3-d240c9e361ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nne tano sita saba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITA"," userResponse":" SITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025973812","data":{"timestamp":" 947025973812"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 624e487c-bf73-40d0-b6f3-d240c9e361ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nne tano sita saba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" SABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025977280","data":{"timestamp":" 947025977280"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 624e487c-bf73-40d0-b6f3-d240c9e361ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nane tisa kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANE"," userResponse":" NANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025977908","data":{"timestamp":" 947025977907"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 624e487c-bf73-40d0-b6f3-d240c9e361ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nane tisa kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TISA"," userResponse":" TISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025978443","data":{"timestamp":" 947025978443"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 624e487c-bf73-40d0-b6f3-d240c9e361ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nane tisa kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMI"," userResponse":" KUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025981499","data":{"timestamp":" 947025981499"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 624e487c-bf73-40d0-b6f3-d240c9e361ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Nane tisa kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025981787","data":{"timestamp":" 947025981787"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 624e487c-bf73-40d0-b6f3-d240c9e361ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nane tisa kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMI"," userResponse":" KUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025991004","data":{"timestamp":" 947025991002"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 624e487c-bf73-40d0-b6f3-d240c9e361ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nane tisa kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026015768","data":{"timestamp":" 947026015768"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026016344","data":{"timestamp":" 947026016344"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026016581","data":{"timestamp":" 947026016581"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026017221","data":{"timestamp":" 947026017220"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026018543","data":{"timestamp":" 947026018543"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIONDOKEA"," userResponse":" PALIONDOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026019017","data":{"timestamp":" 947026019016"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JITU"," userResponse":" JITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026019195","data":{"timestamp":" 947026019194"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026019741","data":{"timestamp":" 947026019740"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKE"," userResponse":" KIKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026023912","data":{"timestamp":" 947026023912"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" LILIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026025112","data":{"timestamp":" 947026025112"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIKITEMBEA"," userResponse":" LIKITEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026026063","data":{"timestamp":" 947026026063"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KANDOKANDO"," userResponse":" KANDOKANDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026026314","data":{"timestamp":" 947026026314"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWA"," userResponse":" MWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026026855","data":{"timestamp":" 947026026855"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIWA"," userResponse":" ZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026028249","data":{"timestamp":" 947026028249"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIWAONA"," userResponse":" LILIWAONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026029082","data":{"timestamp":" 947026029081"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASICHANA"," userResponse":" WASICHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026029822","data":{"timestamp":" 947026029822"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATATU"," userResponse":" WATATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026033037","data":{"timestamp":" 947026033037"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Likawauliza Ni nani kati yenu anayependwa na wazazi wote wawili?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIKAWAULIZA"," userResponse":" LIKAWAULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026033697","data":{"timestamp":" 947026033697"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Likawauliza Ni nani kati yenu anayependwa na wazazi wote wawili?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026034233","data":{"timestamp":" 947026034232"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Likawauliza Ni nani kati yenu anayependwa na wazazi wote wawili?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026034781","data":{"timestamp":" 947026034781"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Likawauliza Ni nani kati yenu anayependwa na wazazi wote wawili?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATI"," userResponse":" KATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026035268","data":{"timestamp":" 947026035267"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Likawauliza Ni nani kati yenu anayependwa na wazazi wote wawili?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YENU"," userResponse":" YENU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026036317","data":{"timestamp":" 947026036317"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Likawauliza Ni nani kati yenu anayependwa na wazazi wote wawili?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAYEPENDWA"," userResponse":" ANAYEPENDWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026036541","data":{"timestamp":" 947026036541"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Likawauliza Ni nani kati yenu anayependwa na wazazi wote wawili?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026037175","data":{"timestamp":" 947026037174"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Likawauliza Ni nani kati yenu anayependwa na wazazi wote wawili?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026037674","data":{"timestamp":" 947026037674"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Likawauliza Ni nani kati yenu anayependwa na wazazi wote wawili?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026038659","data":{"timestamp":" 947026038659"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Likawauliza Ni nani kati yenu anayependwa na wazazi wote wawili?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAWILI"," userResponse":" WAWILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026041755","data":{"timestamp":" 947026041755"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msichana wa kwanza akasema Mamangu hunipenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSICHANA"," userResponse":" MSICHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026041938","data":{"timestamp":" 947026041938"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msichana wa kwanza akasema Mamangu hunipenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026042471","data":{"timestamp":" 947026042471"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msichana wa kwanza akasema Mamangu hunipenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026043364","data":{"timestamp":" 947026043364"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msichana wa kwanza akasema Mamangu hunipenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026044484","data":{"timestamp":" 947026044484"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msichana wa kwanza akasema Mamangu hunipenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" MAMANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026045334","data":{"timestamp":" 947026045334"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msichana wa kwanza akasema Mamangu hunipenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNIPENDA"," userResponse":" HUNIPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026046070","data":{"timestamp":" 947026046070"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msichana wa kwanza akasema Mamangu hunipenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026048774","data":{"timestamp":" 947026048773"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwingine akasema Babangu hunipenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026049625","data":{"timestamp":" 947026049625"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwingine akasema Babangu hunipenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026050756","data":{"timestamp":" 947026050756"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwingine akasema Babangu hunipenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABANGU"," userResponse":" BABANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026051480","data":{"timestamp":" 947026051479"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwingine akasema Babangu hunipenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNIPENDA"," userResponse":" HUNIPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026052218","data":{"timestamp":" 947026052218"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwingine akasema Babangu hunipenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026054798","data":{"timestamp":" 947026054798"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wa tatu akasema Ninapendwa na wazazi wote sawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026054963","data":{"timestamp":" 947026054963"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wa tatu akasema Ninapendwa na wazazi wote sawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026055578","data":{"timestamp":" 947026055578"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wa tatu akasema Ninapendwa na wazazi wote sawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026056423","data":{"timestamp":" 947026056423"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wa tatu akasema Ninapendwa na wazazi wote sawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026058186","data":{"timestamp":" 947026058186"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wa tatu akasema Ninapendwa na wazazi wote sawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAPENDWA"," userResponse":" NINAPENDWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026058432","data":{"timestamp":" 947026058432"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wa tatu akasema Ninapendwa na wazazi wote sawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026059118","data":{"timestamp":" 947026059117"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wa tatu akasema Ninapendwa na wazazi wote sawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026059674","data":{"timestamp":" 947026059674"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wa tatu akasema Ninapendwa na wazazi wote sawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026060290","data":{"timestamp":" 947026060290"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wa tatu akasema Ninapendwa na wazazi wote sawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAWA"," userResponse":" SAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026063219","data":{"timestamp":" 947026063218"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026063726","data":{"timestamp":" 947026063726"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JITU"," userResponse":" JITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026064923","data":{"timestamp":" 947026064923"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIKAMWAMBIA"," userResponse":" LIKAMWAMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026065929","data":{"timestamp":" 947026065929"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSICHANA"," userResponse":" MSICHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026066878","data":{"timestamp":" 947026066878"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAYEPENDWA"," userResponse":" ANAYEPENDWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026067113","data":{"timestamp":" 947026067113"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026067801","data":{"timestamp":" 947026067801"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026068558","data":{"timestamp":" 947026068558"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026070447","data":{"timestamp":" 947026070447"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFUATE"," userResponse":" ALIFUATE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026072556","data":{"timestamp":" 947026072555"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKALISAIDIE"," userResponse":" AKALISAIDIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026073492","data":{"timestamp":" 947026073492"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUINUA"," userResponse":" KUINUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026074089","data":{"timestamp":" 947026074089"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TITA"," userResponse":" TITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026074310","data":{"timestamp":" 947026074309"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026074858","data":{"timestamp":" 947026074858"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNI"," userResponse":" KUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026075813","data":{"timestamp":" 947026075813"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGONGONI"," userResponse":" MGONGONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026078173","data":{"timestamp":" 947026078173"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo msichana huyo alilifuata jitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026078989","data":{"timestamp":" 947026078989"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo msichana huyo alilifuata jitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026079957","data":{"timestamp":" 947026079957"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo msichana huyo alilifuata jitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSICHANA"," userResponse":" MSICHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026080564","data":{"timestamp":" 947026080563"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo msichana huyo alilifuata jitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026081860","data":{"timestamp":" 947026081860"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo msichana huyo alilifuata jitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALILIFUATA"," userResponse":" ALILIFUATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026082478","data":{"timestamp":" 947026082478"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo msichana huyo alilifuata jitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JITU"," userResponse":" JITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026085576","data":{"timestamp":" 947026085575"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutembea kidogo msichana akaliuliza jitu Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026085772","data":{"timestamp":" 947026085772"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutembea kidogo msichana akaliuliza jitu Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026086588","data":{"timestamp":" 947026086588"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutembea kidogo msichana akaliuliza jitu Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTEMBEA"," userResponse":" KUTEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026087382","data":{"timestamp":" 947026087382"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutembea kidogo msichana akaliuliza jitu Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" KIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026088360","data":{"timestamp":" 947026088360"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutembea kidogo msichana akaliuliza jitu Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSICHANA"," userResponse":" MSICHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026089564","data":{"timestamp":" 947026089564"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutembea kidogo msichana akaliuliza jitu Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKALIULIZA"," userResponse":" AKALIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026090130","data":{"timestamp":" 947026090130"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutembea kidogo msichana akaliuliza jitu Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JITU"," userResponse":" JITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026091175","data":{"timestamp":" 947026091174"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutembea kidogo msichana akaliuliza jitu Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" WAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026091613","data":{"timestamp":" 947026091613"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutembea kidogo msichana akaliuliza jitu Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNI"," userResponse":" KUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026092400","data":{"timestamp":" 947026092400"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutembea kidogo msichana akaliuliza jitu Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKO"," userResponse":" ZAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026094873","data":{"timestamp":" 947026094872"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Ziko karibu na ile miti pale!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JITU"," userResponse":" JITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026095809","data":{"timestamp":" 947026095809"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Ziko karibu na ile miti pale!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIKAJIBU"," userResponse":" LIKAJIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026096563","data":{"timestamp":" 947026096563"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Ziko karibu na ile miti pale!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIKO"," userResponse":" ZIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026105575","data":{"timestamp":" 947026105574"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Ziko karibu na ile miti pale!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026105770","data":{"timestamp":" 947026105770"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Ziko karibu na ile miti pale!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026106286","data":{"timestamp":" 947026106285"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Ziko karibu na ile miti pale!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026108585","data":{"timestamp":" 947026108584"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Ziko karibu na ile miti pale!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITI"," userResponse":" MITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026117819","data":{"timestamp":" 947026117819"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Ziko karibu na ile miti pale!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026138982","data":{"timestamp":" 947026138982"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kwenye miti hiyo msichana akauliza jitu tena Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOFIKA"," userResponse":" WALIPOFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026143802","data":{"timestamp":" 947026143802"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kwenye miti hiyo msichana akauliza jitu tena Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026144382","data":{"timestamp":" 947026144381"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kwenye miti hiyo msichana akauliza jitu tena Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITI"," userResponse":" MITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026145017","data":{"timestamp":" 947026145017"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kwenye miti hiyo msichana akauliza jitu tena Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026145782","data":{"timestamp":" 947026145782"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kwenye miti hiyo msichana akauliza jitu tena Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSICHANA"," userResponse":" MSICHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026146691","data":{"timestamp":" 947026146691"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kwenye miti hiyo msichana akauliza jitu tena Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAULIZA"," userResponse":" AKAULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026147150","data":{"timestamp":" 947026147150"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kwenye miti hiyo msichana akauliza jitu tena Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JITU"," userResponse":" JITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026147666","data":{"timestamp":" 947026147666"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kwenye miti hiyo msichana akauliza jitu tena Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026148602","data":{"timestamp":" 947026148601"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kwenye miti hiyo msichana akauliza jitu tena Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" WAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026149026","data":{"timestamp":" 947026149026"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kwenye miti hiyo msichana akauliza jitu tena Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNI"," userResponse":" KUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026149843","data":{"timestamp":" 947026149843"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kwenye miti hiyo msichana akauliza jitu tena Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKO"," userResponse":" ZAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026152699","data":{"timestamp":" 947026152699"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Haziko mbali sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JITU"," userResponse":" JITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026153685","data":{"timestamp":" 947026153685"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Haziko mbali sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIKAJIBU"," userResponse":" LIKAJIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026154706","data":{"timestamp":" 947026154706"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Haziko mbali sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAZIKO"," userResponse":" HAZIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026155074","data":{"timestamp":" 947026155074"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Haziko mbali sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" MBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026155745","data":{"timestamp":" 947026155745"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Haziko mbali sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026159493","data":{"timestamp":" 947026159493"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakakutana na mwanamume."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIENDELEA"," userResponse":" WALIENDELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026160391","data":{"timestamp":" 947026160391"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakakutana na mwanamume."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTEMBEA"," userResponse":" KUTEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026163460","data":{"timestamp":" 947026163459"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakakutana na mwanamume."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAKUTANA"," userResponse":" WAKAKUTANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026163646","data":{"timestamp":" 947026163646"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakakutana na mwanamume."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026164576","data":{"timestamp":" 947026164576"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakakutana na mwanamume."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMUME"," userResponse":" MWANAMUME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026167272","data":{"timestamp":" 947026167272"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Anaitwa Mfuko Uzunguzao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMUME"," userResponse":" MWANAMUME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026168532","data":{"timestamp":" 947026168532"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Anaitwa Mfuko Uzunguzao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKALIULIZA"," userResponse":" AKALIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026169071","data":{"timestamp":" 947026169071"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Anaitwa Mfuko Uzunguzao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JITU"," userResponse":" JITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026170219","data":{"timestamp":" 947026170219"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Anaitwa Mfuko Uzunguzao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026170777","data":{"timestamp":" 947026170776"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Anaitwa Mfuko Uzunguzao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026171255","data":{"timestamp":" 947026171255"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Anaitwa Mfuko Uzunguzao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKO"," userResponse":" WAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026172305","data":{"timestamp":" 947026172305"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Anaitwa Mfuko Uzunguzao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAITWAJE"," userResponse":" ANAITWAJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026174837","data":{"timestamp":" 947026174837"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Anaitwa Mfuko Uzunguzao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JITU"," userResponse":" JITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026175728","data":{"timestamp":" 947026175728"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Anaitwa Mfuko Uzunguzao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIKAJIBU"," userResponse":" LIKAJIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026177139","data":{"timestamp":" 947026177139"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Anaitwa Mfuko Uzunguzao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAITWA"," userResponse":" ANAITWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026177775","data":{"timestamp":" 947026177774"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Anaitwa Mfuko Uzunguzao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFUKO"," userResponse":" MFUKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026178957","data":{"timestamp":" 947026178957"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Anaitwa Mfuko Uzunguzao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UZUNGUZAO"," userResponse":" UZUNGUZAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026182160","data":{"timestamp":" 947026182160"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSICHANA"," userResponse":" MSICHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026183013","data":{"timestamp":" 947026183013"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAANZA"," userResponse":" AKAANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026183623","data":{"timestamp":" 947026183623"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUIMBA"," userResponse":" KUIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026183889","data":{"timestamp":" 947026183889"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026184633","data":{"timestamp":" 947026184629"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026186050","data":{"timestamp":" 947026186050"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026186534","data":{"timestamp":" 947026186534"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMWE"," userResponse":" KAMWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026186899","data":{"timestamp":" 947026186899"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SI"," userResponse":" SI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026187895","data":{"timestamp":" 947026187895"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFUKO"," userResponse":" MFUKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026189012","data":{"timestamp":" 947026189012"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIFUKO"," userResponse":" MIFUKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026190470","data":{"timestamp":" 947026190469"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAIONGEI"," userResponse":" HAIONGEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026191508","data":{"timestamp":" 947026191508"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAITWA"," userResponse":" NAITWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026192216","data":{"timestamp":" 947026192216"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAAMUNGEI"," userResponse":" KAAMUNGEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026192853","data":{"timestamp":" 947026192853"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LO"," userResponse":" LO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026195391","data":{"timestamp":" 947026195391"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026196627","data":{"timestamp":" 947026196626"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIMPENDAYE"," userResponse":" NIMPENDAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026197005","data":{"timestamp":" 947026197005"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LO"," userResponse":" LO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026199476","data":{"timestamp":" 947026199476"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026200700","data":{"timestamp":" 947026200700"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIMPENDAYE"," userResponse":" NIMPENDAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026201427","data":{"timestamp":" 947026201427"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATA"," userResponse":" KATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026202224","data":{"timestamp":" 947026202224"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANYWEA"," userResponse":" NANYWEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026203243","data":{"timestamp":" 947026203243"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026206608","data":{"timestamp":" 947026206608"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume huyo aliposikia wimbo wa msichana alimnusuru kutoka kwa jitu na kumrudisha kwa wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMUME"," userResponse":" MWANAMUME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026207143","data":{"timestamp":" 947026207143"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume huyo aliposikia wimbo wa msichana alimnusuru kutoka kwa jitu na kumrudisha kwa wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026208227","data":{"timestamp":" 947026208227"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume huyo aliposikia wimbo wa msichana alimnusuru kutoka kwa jitu na kumrudisha kwa wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOSIKIA"," userResponse":" ALIPOSIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026208713","data":{"timestamp":" 947026208712"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume huyo aliposikia wimbo wa msichana alimnusuru kutoka kwa jitu na kumrudisha kwa wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIMBO"," userResponse":" WIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026208918","data":{"timestamp":" 947026208918"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume huyo aliposikia wimbo wa msichana alimnusuru kutoka kwa jitu na kumrudisha kwa wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026209793","data":{"timestamp":" 947026209792"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume huyo aliposikia wimbo wa msichana alimnusuru kutoka kwa jitu na kumrudisha kwa wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSICHANA"," userResponse":" MSICHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026211991","data":{"timestamp":" 947026211990"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume huyo aliposikia wimbo wa msichana alimnusuru kutoka kwa jitu na kumrudisha kwa wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMNUSURU"," userResponse":" ALIMNUSURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026212646","data":{"timestamp":" 947026212646"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume huyo aliposikia wimbo wa msichana alimnusuru kutoka kwa jitu na kumrudisha kwa wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026212892","data":{"timestamp":" 947026212892"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume huyo aliposikia wimbo wa msichana alimnusuru kutoka kwa jitu na kumrudisha kwa wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026213539","data":{"timestamp":" 947026213539"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume huyo aliposikia wimbo wa msichana alimnusuru kutoka kwa jitu na kumrudisha kwa wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JITU"," userResponse":" JITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026214136","data":{"timestamp":" 947026214136"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume huyo aliposikia wimbo wa msichana alimnusuru kutoka kwa jitu na kumrudisha kwa wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026215162","data":{"timestamp":" 947026215162"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume huyo aliposikia wimbo wa msichana alimnusuru kutoka kwa jitu na kumrudisha kwa wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMRUDISHA"," userResponse":" KUMRUDISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026215452","data":{"timestamp":" 947026215451"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume huyo aliposikia wimbo wa msichana alimnusuru kutoka kwa jitu na kumrudisha kwa wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026216118","data":{"timestamp":" 947026216114"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume huyo aliposikia wimbo wa msichana alimnusuru kutoka kwa jitu na kumrudisha kwa wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026216668","data":{"timestamp":" 947026216668"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume huyo aliposikia wimbo wa msichana alimnusuru kutoka kwa jitu na kumrudisha kwa wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026219423","data":{"timestamp":" 947026219423"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadithi inaishia hapo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADITHI"," userResponse":" HADITHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026220391","data":{"timestamp":" 947026220391"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadithi inaishia hapo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INAISHIA"," userResponse":" INAISHIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026220897","data":{"timestamp":" 947026220897"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadithi inaishia hapo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026223631","data":{"timestamp":" 947026223630"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Hadithi inaishia hapo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026223792","data":{"timestamp":" 947026223792"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 5383b455-1005-4037-a19d-5b2a2f8bce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_57"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadithi inaishia hapo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026238090","data":{"timestamp":" 947026238090"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 9ee2e994-75c8-40d6-a5bf-4f184c2e1a16"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UZI"," userResponse":" UZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026248162","data":{"timestamp":" 947026248162"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 9ee2e994-75c8-40d6-a5bf-4f184c2e1a16"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UZI"," userResponse":" UZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026249810","data":{"timestamp":" 947026249810"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 9ee2e994-75c8-40d6-a5bf-4f184c2e1a16"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UYOGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UYOGA"," userResponse":" UYOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026253732","data":{"timestamp":" 947026253731"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 9ee2e994-75c8-40d6-a5bf-4f184c2e1a16"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UYOGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UYOGA"," userResponse":" UYOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026255322","data":{"timestamp":" 947026255322"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 9ee2e994-75c8-40d6-a5bf-4f184c2e1a16"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UKUTA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKUTA"," userResponse":" UKUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026258186","data":{"timestamp":" 947026258186"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 9ee2e994-75c8-40d6-a5bf-4f184c2e1a16"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UKUTA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKUTA"," userResponse":" UKUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026259813","data":{"timestamp":" 947026259812"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 9ee2e994-75c8-40d6-a5bf-4f184c2e1a16"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UKULIMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKULIMA"," userResponse":" UKULIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026264408","data":{"timestamp":" 947026264408"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 9ee2e994-75c8-40d6-a5bf-4f184c2e1a16"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UKULIMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKULIMA"," userResponse":" UKULIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026266026","data":{"timestamp":" 947026266026"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 9ee2e994-75c8-40d6-a5bf-4f184c2e1a16"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UBAO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UBAO"," userResponse":" UBAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026273725","data":{"timestamp":" 947026273725"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 9ee2e994-75c8-40d6-a5bf-4f184c2e1a16"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UBAO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UBAO"," userResponse":" UBAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026275339","data":{"timestamp":" 947026275339"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 9ee2e994-75c8-40d6-a5bf-4f184c2e1a16"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UA"," userResponse":" UA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026277992","data":{"timestamp":" 947026277992"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 9ee2e994-75c8-40d6-a5bf-4f184c2e1a16"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UA"," userResponse":" UA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026279638","data":{"timestamp":" 947026279637"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 9ee2e994-75c8-40d6-a5bf-4f184c2e1a16"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UDONGO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UDONGO"," userResponse":" UDONGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026284564","data":{"timestamp":" 947026284564"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 9ee2e994-75c8-40d6-a5bf-4f184c2e1a16"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UDONGO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UDONGO"," userResponse":" UDONGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026286430","data":{"timestamp":" 947026286430"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 9ee2e994-75c8-40d6-a5bf-4f184c2e1a16"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UGALI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026290915","data":{"timestamp":" 947026290915"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 9ee2e994-75c8-40d6-a5bf-4f184c2e1a16"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UGALI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026292938","data":{"timestamp":" 947026292937"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 9ee2e994-75c8-40d6-a5bf-4f184c2e1a16"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" UGALI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026293454","data":{"timestamp":" 947026293454"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 9ee2e994-75c8-40d6-a5bf-4f184c2e1a16"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UGALI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.rise.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026304241","data":{"timestamp":" 947026304240"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 9ee2e994-75c8-40d6-a5bf-4f184c2e1a16"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" UGALI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026311777","data":{"timestamp":" 947026311776"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 9ee2e994-75c8-40d6-a5bf-4f184c2e1a16"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" UGALI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026324617","data":{"timestamp":" 947026324616"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GRACA"," userResponse":" GRACA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026325768","data":{"timestamp":" 947026325767"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIZALIWA"," userResponse":" ALIZALIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026326796","data":{"timestamp":" 947026326796"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOZAMBIQUE"," userResponse":" MOZAMBIQUE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026329377","data":{"timestamp":" 947026329377"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHI"," userResponse":" NCHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026329805","data":{"timestamp":" 947026329805"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" YAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026330583","data":{"timestamp":" 947026330583"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026331326","data":{"timestamp":" 947026331325"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASKINI"," userResponse":" MASKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026332102","data":{"timestamp":" 947026332102"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026332782","data":{"timestamp":" 947026332781"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026333698","data":{"timestamp":" 947026333698"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUWA"," userResponse":" HAWAKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026334557","data":{"timestamp":" 947026334557"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEPATA"," userResponse":" WAMEPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026335226","data":{"timestamp":" 947026335226"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UHURU"," userResponse":" UHURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026338032","data":{"timestamp":" 947026338031"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026339068","data":{"timestamp":" 947026339068"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUA"," userResponse":" HAWAKUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026339294","data":{"timestamp":" 947026339294"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026339851","data":{"timestamp":" 947026339851"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026340459","data":{"timestamp":" 947026340459"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NZURI"," userResponse":" NZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026340678","data":{"timestamp":" 947026340678"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026341357","data":{"timestamp":" 947026341357"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026343958","data":{"timestamp":" 947026343957"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" MAMAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026344755","data":{"timestamp":" 947026344755"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026344980","data":{"timestamp":" 947026344980"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026345579","data":{"timestamp":" 947026345579"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOTO"," userResponse":" NDOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026345776","data":{"timestamp":" 947026345776"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026346490","data":{"timestamp":" 947026346490"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAPA"," userResponse":" KUWAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026347144","data":{"timestamp":" 947026347144"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWE"," userResponse":" WANAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026348385","data":{"timestamp":" 947026348385"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAISHA"," userResponse":" MAISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026349486","data":{"timestamp":" 947026349486"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZURI"," userResponse":" MAZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026350336","data":{"timestamp":" 947026350336"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026350716","data":{"timestamp":" 947026350716"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026351731","data":{"timestamp":" 947026351731"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASOMO"," userResponse":" MASOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026353557","data":{"timestamp":" 947026353557"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAINGEWEZEKANA"," userResponse":" HAINGEWEZEKANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026356710","data":{"timestamp":" 947026356710"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026357318","data":{"timestamp":" 947026357317"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GRACA"," userResponse":" GRACA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026358248","data":{"timestamp":" 947026358248"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEKUWA"," userResponse":" ANGEKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026359209","data":{"timestamp":" 947026359209"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZALIWA"," userResponse":" MZALIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026359391","data":{"timestamp":" 947026359390"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026359962","data":{"timestamp":" 947026359961"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITA"," userResponse":" SITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026362437","data":{"timestamp":" 947026362437"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LICHA"," userResponse":" LICHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026362659","data":{"timestamp":" 947026362659"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026363349","data":{"timestamp":" 947026363349"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026364021","data":{"timestamp":" 947026364020"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" HII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026364557","data":{"timestamp":" 947026364557"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026365703","data":{"timestamp":" 947026365703"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" KULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026365992","data":{"timestamp":" 947026365992"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026376355","data":{"timestamp":" 947026376355"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUZUNI"," userResponse":" HUZUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026377114","data":{"timestamp":" 947026377114"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANI"," userResponse":" KWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026377803","data":{"timestamp":" 947026377802"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABAKE"," userResponse":" BABAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026378454","data":{"timestamp":" 947026378454"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GRACA"," userResponse":" GRACA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026379511","data":{"timestamp":" 947026379511"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026380509","data":{"timestamp":" 947026380509"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAKUFA"," userResponse":" ANAKUFA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026383010","data":{"timestamp":" 947026383010"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIOTA"," userResponse":" ALIOTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026383506","data":{"timestamp":" 947026383506"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026384148","data":{"timestamp":" 947026384148"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026384595","data":{"timestamp":" 947026384595"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026385461","data":{"timestamp":" 947026385461"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026386107","data":{"timestamp":" 947026386106"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEENDA"," userResponse":" ANGEENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026386548","data":{"timestamp":" 947026386547"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026387559","data":{"timestamp":" 947026387559"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NZURI"," userResponse":" NZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026390213","data":{"timestamp":" 947026390213"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJUA"," userResponse":" ALIJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026390953","data":{"timestamp":" 947026390953"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ELIMU"," userResponse":" ELIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026391478","data":{"timestamp":" 947026391478"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYO"," userResponse":" NDIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026392825","data":{"timestamp":" 947026392825"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INGEMSAIDIA"," userResponse":" INGEMSAIDIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026393660","data":{"timestamp":" 947026393660"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAWE"," userResponse":" MWANAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026396662","data":{"timestamp":" 947026396662"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JAMII"," userResponse":" JAMII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026397161","data":{"timestamp":" 947026397161"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026398139","data":{"timestamp":" 947026398139"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIAPA"," userResponse":" ILIAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026399145","data":{"timestamp":" 947026399144"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTIMIZA"," userResponse":" KUTIMIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026399722","data":{"timestamp":" 947026399722"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOTO"," userResponse":" NDOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026400310","data":{"timestamp":" 947026400310"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026403223","data":{"timestamp":" 947026403223"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIKI"," userResponse":" WIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026403751","data":{"timestamp":" 947026403750"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHACHE"," userResponse":" CHACHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026404334","data":{"timestamp":" 947026404333"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026404594","data":{"timestamp":" 947026404594"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026405100","data":{"timestamp":" 947026405099"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIFO"," userResponse":" KIFO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026405340","data":{"timestamp":" 947026405340"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026406183","data":{"timestamp":" 947026406183"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABAKE"," userResponse":" BABAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026407216","data":{"timestamp":" 947026407216"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026408085","data":{"timestamp":" 947026408085"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPEWA"," userResponse":" ALIPEWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026408623","data":{"timestamp":" 947026408623"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINA"," userResponse":" JINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026409592","data":{"timestamp":" 947026409592"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUAMBATA"," userResponse":" KUAMBATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026409932","data":{"timestamp":" 947026409932"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026410483","data":{"timestamp":" 947026410483"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UREMBO"," userResponse":" UREMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026411127","data":{"timestamp":" 947026411127"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026413824","data":{"timestamp":" 947026413824"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIITWA"," userResponse":" ALIITWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026414504","data":{"timestamp":" 947026414503"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GRACA"," userResponse":" GRACA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026417053","data":{"timestamp":" 947026417053"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KADRI"," userResponse":" KADRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026417670","data":{"timestamp":" 947026417670"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIAKA"," userResponse":" MIAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026418743","data":{"timestamp":" 947026418742"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIPOZIDI"," userResponse":" ILIPOZIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026419721","data":{"timestamp":" 947026419721"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUYOYOMA"," userResponse":" KUYOYOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026420746","data":{"timestamp":" 947026420745"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIVYO"," userResponse":" NDIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026421355","data":{"timestamp":" 947026421355"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GRACA"," userResponse":" GRACA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026422191","data":{"timestamp":" 947026422191"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIZIDI"," userResponse":" ALIZIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026422816","data":{"timestamp":" 947026422816"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULETA"," userResponse":" KULETA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026423741","data":{"timestamp":" 947026423740"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026424465","data":{"timestamp":" 947026424465"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAO"," userResponse":" KWAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026427130","data":{"timestamp":" 947026427129"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026428288","data":{"timestamp":" 947026428287"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIAMUA"," userResponse":" ILIAMUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026429074","data":{"timestamp":" 947026429074"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMPA"," userResponse":" KUMPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026429669","data":{"timestamp":" 947026429669"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GRACA"," userResponse":" GRACA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026430466","data":{"timestamp":" 947026430466"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASOMO"," userResponse":" MASOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026431664","data":{"timestamp":" 947026431663"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZURI"," userResponse":" MAZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026434864","data":{"timestamp":" 947026434863"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GRACA"," userResponse":" GRACA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026435844","data":{"timestamp":" 947026435844"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITIA"," userResponse":" ALITIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026436362","data":{"timestamp":" 947026436362"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BIDII"," userResponse":" BIDII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026436900","data":{"timestamp":" 947026436899"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026437666","data":{"timestamp":" 947026437666"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULENI"," userResponse":" SHULENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026440358","data":{"timestamp":" 947026440357"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPATA"," userResponse":" ALIPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026441106","data":{"timestamp":" 947026441106"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUZO"," userResponse":" TUZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026441873","data":{"timestamp":" 947026441873"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBALO"," userResponse":" AMBALO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026443090","data":{"timestamp":" 947026443088"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINGEBADILISHA"," userResponse":" LINGEBADILISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026444117","data":{"timestamp":" 947026444117"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAISHA"," userResponse":" MAISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026444713","data":{"timestamp":" 947026444712"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026447720","data":{"timestamp":" 947026447720"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026448777","data":{"timestamp":" 947026448777"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UHISANI"," userResponse":" UHISANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026449704","data":{"timestamp":" 947026449704"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKUSOMEA"," userResponse":" WAKUSOMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026450171","data":{"timestamp":" 947026450171"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026451474","data":{"timestamp":" 947026451474"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NZURI"," userResponse":" NZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026452363","data":{"timestamp":" 947026452363"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJNI"," userResponse":" KIJIJNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026454684","data":{"timestamp":" 947026454684"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOTO"," userResponse":" NDOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026455201","data":{"timestamp":" 947026455201"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026456222","data":{"timestamp":" 947026456222"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026456713","data":{"timestamp":" 947026456712"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026457190","data":{"timestamp":" 947026457189"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026458040","data":{"timestamp":" 947026458039"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWALIMU"," userResponse":" MWALIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026461261","data":{"timestamp":" 947026461261"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITAMANI"," userResponse":" ALITAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026461986","data":{"timestamp":" 947026461986"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026462193","data":{"timestamp":" 947026462193"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026463213","data":{"timestamp":" 947026463213"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOZAMBIQUE"," userResponse":" MOZAMBIQUE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026464023","data":{"timestamp":" 947026464023"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAJUE"," userResponse":" WAJUE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026464758","data":{"timestamp":" 947026464758"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026464999","data":{"timestamp":" 947026464999"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026465926","data":{"timestamp":" 947026465926"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUANDIKA"," userResponse":" KUANDIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026468980","data":{"timestamp":" 947026468980"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITAMANI"," userResponse":" ALITAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026469764","data":{"timestamp":" 947026469764"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026470422","data":{"timestamp":" 947026470422"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAPO"," userResponse":" AMBAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026471187","data":{"timestamp":" 947026471187"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026471713","data":{"timestamp":" 947026471713"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026472520","data":{"timestamp":" 947026472520"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGEENDA"," userResponse":" WANGEENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026473439","data":{"timestamp":" 947026473439"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULENI"," userResponse":" SHULENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026476553","data":{"timestamp":" 947026476553"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GRACA"," userResponse":" GRACA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026477450","data":{"timestamp":" 947026477450"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITIA"," userResponse":" ALITIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026478257","data":{"timestamp":" 947026478257"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BIDII"," userResponse":" BIDII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026478607","data":{"timestamp":" 947026478607"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026479331","data":{"timestamp":" 947026479331"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026480582","data":{"timestamp":" 947026480582"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULENI"," userResponse":" SHULENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026483124","data":{"timestamp":" 947026483124"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADAYE"," userResponse":" BAADAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026484003","data":{"timestamp":" 947026484003"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" KIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026485124","data":{"timestamp":" 947026485124"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPATA"," userResponse":" ALIPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026485635","data":{"timestamp":" 947026485635"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUZO"," userResponse":" TUZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026486316","data":{"timestamp":" 947026486316"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGINE"," userResponse":" NYINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026486439","data":{"timestamp":" 947026486439"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026487413","data":{"timestamp":" 947026487413"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUHUDHURIA"," userResponse":" KUHUDHURIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026487917","data":{"timestamp":" 947026487916"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUO"," userResponse":" CHUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026488697","data":{"timestamp":" 947026488697"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKUU"," userResponse":" KIKUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026489556","data":{"timestamp":" 947026489556"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKO"," userResponse":" HUKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026490379","data":{"timestamp":" 947026490379"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PORTUGAL"," userResponse":" PORTUGAL"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026493238","data":{"timestamp":" 947026493238"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPATA"," userResponse":" ALIPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026494149","data":{"timestamp":" 947026494149"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARAFIKI"," userResponse":" MARAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026501805","data":{"timestamp":" 947026501805"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGI"," userResponse":" WENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026504902","data":{"timestamp":" 947026504902"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAJIFUNZA"," userResponse":" AKAJIFUNZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026505409","data":{"timestamp":" 947026505409"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LUGHA"," userResponse":" LUGHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026506177","data":{"timestamp":" 947026506177"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGI"," userResponse":" NYINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026506926","data":{"timestamp":" 947026506926"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GENI"," userResponse":" GENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026507353","data":{"timestamp":" 947026507353"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026508285","data":{"timestamp":" 947026508285"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASOMA"," userResponse":" AKASOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026509267","data":{"timestamp":" 947026509266"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITABU"," userResponse":" VITABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026509899","data":{"timestamp":" 947026509899"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VINGI"," userResponse":" VINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026510639","data":{"timestamp":" 947026510639"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIPYA"," userResponse":" VIPYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026510959","data":{"timestamp":" 947026510958"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026511356","data":{"timestamp":" 947026511356"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIPYA"," userResponse":" VIPYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:U..U.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026525015","data":{"timestamp":" 947026525014"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026541845","data":{"timestamp":" 947026541845"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026556214","data":{"timestamp":" 947026556214"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026578476","data":{"timestamp":" 947026578476"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:U..U.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026590766","data":{"timestamp":" 947026590766"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026601358","data":{"timestamp":" 947026601357"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026610423","data":{"timestamp":" 947026610418"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026626344","data":{"timestamp":" 947026626344"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026635839","data":{"timestamp":" 947026635838"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026648302","data":{"timestamp":" 947026648301"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" ba6889f0-ab50-433c-8fd9-2bb333b8c2bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_59"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026661655","data":{"timestamp":" 947026661655"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" a5cbe1f3-7326-4deb-83a9-d76140278ef8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026664536","data":{"timestamp":" 947026664536"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" a5cbe1f3-7326-4deb-83a9-d76140278ef8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026666815","data":{"timestamp":" 947026666815"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" a5cbe1f3-7326-4deb-83a9-d76140278ef8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026666897","data":{"timestamp":" 947026666897"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" a5cbe1f3-7326-4deb-83a9-d76140278ef8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026667387","data":{"timestamp":" 947026667387"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" a5cbe1f3-7326-4deb-83a9-d76140278ef8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026716960","data":{"timestamp":" 947026716928"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" a5cbe1f3-7326-4deb-83a9-d76140278ef8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947026717352","data":{"timestamp":" 947026717352"," userId":" 6130000023"," sessionId":" 6130000023_20000105_005503"," gameId":" 97265075-b1e8-4aea-b421-4eb890043b97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_58"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kima alikubali bila kujua yaliyomsubiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJUA"," userResponse":" KUJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}